[
{"Screen Size": "15.6 inches", "Screen Resolution": "1920 x 1080 pixels", "Max Screen Resolution": "1920 x 1080 pixels", "Processor": "2.3 GHz Intel Core i5", "RAM": "8 GB DDR4-SDRAM", "Hard Drive": "256 GB flash_memory_solid_state", "Graphics Coprocessor": "geforce", "Chipset Brand": "NVIDIA GeForce 940MX", "Card Description": "Dedicated", "Graphics Card Ram Size": "2000 MB", "Wireless Type": "802.11 A/C", "Number of USB 2.0 Ports": "1", "Number of USB 3.0 Ports": "2", "Average Battery Life (in hours)": "12 hours", "Brand Name": "Acer", "Series": "E5-575G", "Item model number": "E5-575G-53VG", "Operating System": "Windows 10", "Item Weight": "5.3 pounds", "Product Dimensions": "15 x 10.2 x 1.2 inches", "Item Dimensions  L x W x H": "15.02 x 10.2 x 1.19 inches", "Color": "Obsidian Black", "Processor Brand": "Intel", "Processor Count": "1", "Computer Memory Type": "DDR3 SDRAM", "Flash Memory Size": "256 GB", "Optical Drive Type": "DVD Super Multi", "Battery Type": "Lithium-Ion (Li-Ion)", "Power Source": "Battery", "Batteries": "1 Lithium ion batteries required. (included)", "ASIN": "B01DT4A2R4", "Customer Reviews": "", "Best Sellers Rank": "", "Shipping Weight": "7 pounds (", "Domestic Shipping": "Currently, item can be shipped only within the U.S. and to APO/FPO addresses. For APO/FPO shipments, please check with the manufacturer regarding warranty and support issues.", "International Shipping": "This item is not eligible for international shipping.", "Date First Available": "May 3, 2016", "Price": "$549.99", "Product Name": "Acer Aspire E 15 E5-575G-53VG Laptop, 15.6 Full HD (Intel Core i5, NVIDIA 940MX, 8GB DDR4, 256GB SSD, Windows 10)"},
{"Screen Size": "15.6 inches", "Max Screen Resolution": "1920 x 1080 pixels", "Processor": "2.4 GHz Intel Core i3", "RAM": "4 GB", "Hard Drive": "1000 GB mechanical_hard_drive", "Card Description": "Integrated", "Wireless Type": "802.11 A/C", "Number of USB 3.0 Ports": "2", "Average Battery Life (in hours)": "12 hours", "Brand Name": "Acer", "Series": "E5-575", "Item model number": "E5-575-33BM", "Operating System": "Windows 10", "Item Weight": "5.3 pounds", "Product Dimensions": "10.2 x 15 x 1.2 inches", "Item Dimensions  L x W x H": "10.2 x 15.02 x 1.19 inches", "Color": "Obsidian Black", "Processor Brand": "Intel", "Processor Count": "1", "Computer Memory Type": "DDR4 SDRAM", "Hard Drive Rotational Speed": "5400 RPM", "Batteries": "1 Lithium ion batteries required. (included)", "ASIN": "B01K1IO3QW", "Customer Reviews": "", "Best Sellers Rank": "", "Shipping Weight": "7 pounds (", "Domestic Shipping": "Currently, item can be shipped only within the U.S. and to APO/FPO addresses. For APO/FPO shipments, please check with the manufacturer regarding warranty and support issues.", "International Shipping": "This item is not eligible for international shipping.", "Date First Available": "August 9, 2016", "Price": "$349.99", "Product Name": "Acer Aspire E 15 E5-575-33BM 15.6-Inch Full HD Notebook (Intel Core i3-7100U Processor 7th Generation , 4GB DDR4,  1TB 5400RPM Hard Drive,  Intel HD Graphics 620, Windows 10 Home), Obsidian Black"},
{"Screen Size": "15.6 inches", "Screen Resolution": "1366x768", "Max Screen Resolution": "1366 x 768", "Processor": "2.16 GHz Pentium", "RAM": "4 GB SDRAM", "Hard Drive": "500 GB HDD 5400 rpm", "Graphics Coprocessor": "integrated_graphics", "Chipset Brand": "intel", "Card Description": "integrated", "Wireless Type": "802.11bgn", "Number of USB 2.0 Ports": "1", "Average Battery Life (in hours)": "6 hours", "Brand Name": "HP", "Series": "15-f222wm", "Item model number": "N5Y13UA#ABA", "Hardware Platform": "PC", "Operating System": "Windows 10", "Item Weight": "4.7 pounds", "Product Dimensions": "15.2 x 10.2 x 0.9 inches", "Item Dimensions  L x W x H": "15.18 x 10.16 x 0.89 inches", "Color": "Black", "Processor Brand": "Intel", "Processor Count": "4", "Computer Memory Type": "DDR3 SDRAM", "Hard Drive Interface": "ATA-4", "Hard Drive Rotational Speed": "5400 RPM", "Power Source": "AC & Battery", "ASIN": "B01MRS3MIS", "Customer Reviews": "", "Best Sellers Rank": "", "Shipping Weight": "6.5 pounds (", "Date First Available": "December 1, 2016", "Price": "$276.98", "Product Name": "2017 NEWEST HP 15-F222WM 15.6\" Touch Screen Laptop - Intel Quad Core Pentium N3540 Processor, 4GB Memory, 500GB Hard Drive, DVD\u00b1RW/CD-RW, HD Webcam Windows 10"},
{"Screen Size": "14 inches", "Max Screen Resolution": "1920x1080 pixels", "Processor": "1.8 GHz E2-7110", "RAM": "4 GB", "Hard Drive": "32 GB", "Chipset Brand": "amd", "Card Description": "Integrated", "Wireless Type": "802.11 A/C", "Number of USB 3.0 Ports": "1", "Brand Name": "HP", "Series": "Notebook", "Item model number": "W2M53UA#ABA", "Operating System": "Windows 10 Home", "Item Weight": "3.9 pounds", "Product Dimensions": "9.5 x 13.6 x 0.9 inches", "Item Dimensions  L x W x H": "9.51 x 13.6 x 0.94 inches", "Processor Brand": "AMD", "Processor Count": "4", "Computer Memory Type": "DDR3 SDRAM", "Flash Memory Size": "32.0", "Batteries": "1 Lithium ion batteries required. (included)", "ASIN": "B01F4ZG68A", "Customer Reviews": "", "Best Sellers Rank": "", "Shipping Weight": "5.2 pounds (", "Domestic Shipping": "Currently, item can be shipped only within the U.S. and to APO/FPO addresses. For APO/FPO shipments, please check with the manufacturer regarding warranty and support issues.", "International Shipping": "This item is not eligible for international shipping.", "Date First Available": "May 29, 2016", "Price": "$219.99", "Product Name": "HP 14-an013nr 14-Inch Notebook (AMD E2-7110 QC, 4GB RAM, 32 GB eMMC Hard Drive, Windows 10 Home 64)"},
{"Screen Size": "15.6 inches", "Max Screen Resolution": "1920x1080 pixels", "Processor": "2.3 GHz Intel Core i5", "RAM": "8 GB DDR3L SDRAM", "Hard Drive": "1 TB mechanical_hard_drive", "Graphics Coprocessor": "shared", "Chipset Brand": "intel", "Card Description": "integrated", "Wireless Type": "802.11 A/C", "Number of USB 2.0 Ports": "2", "Number of USB 3.0 Ports": "1", "Brand Name": "HP", "Series": "Notebook", "Item model number": "W2M75UA#ABA", "Hardware Platform": "PC", "Operating System": "Windows 10", "Item Weight": "4.7 pounds", "Product Dimensions": "10 x 15.1 x 0.9 inches", "Item Dimensions  L x W x H": "10.02 x 15.12 x 0.95 inches", "Color": "Silver", "Processor Brand": "Intel", "Processor Count": "2", "Hard Drive Rotational Speed": "5400 RPM", "Optical Drive Type": "DVD+RW", "Batteries": "1 Lithium ion batteries required. (included)", "ASIN": "B01CGGOZOM", "Customer Reviews": "", "Best Sellers Rank": "", "Shipping Weight": "6.3 pounds (", "Domestic Shipping": "Currently, item can be shipped only within the U.S. and to APO/FPO addresses. For APO/FPO shipments, please check with the manufacturer regarding warranty and support issues.", "International Shipping": "This item is not eligible for international shipping.", "Date First Available": "April 10, 2016", "Price": "$459.99", "Product Name": "HP Notebook 15-ay011nr 15.6-Inch Laptop (6th Gen Intel Core i5-6200U Processor, 8GB DDR3L SDRAM, 1TB HDD, Windows 10), Silver"},
{"Screen Size": "15.6 inches", "Screen Resolution": "1920x1080", "Max Screen Resolution": "1920 x 1080 pixels", "Processor": "2.6 GHz Intel Core i7", "RAM": "8 GB DDR3L SDRAM", "Memory Speed": "1600 MHz", "Hard Drive": "1 TB Hybrid HDD + Flash Cache", "Graphics Coprocessor": "NVIDIA GeForce GTX 960M 4GB GDDR5", "Chipset Brand": "NVIDIA", "Card Description": "dedicated", "Graphics Card Ram Size": "4", "Wireless Type": "802.11 A/C", "Number of USB 3.0 Ports": "3", "Average Battery Life (in hours)": "10 hours", "Brand Name": "Dell", "Series": "Inspiron 15, 7559", "Item model number": "i7559-2512BLK", "Hardware Platform": "PC", "Operating System": "Windows 10", "Item Weight": "4.6 pounds", "Product Dimensions": "15.1 x 15.1 x 10.4 inches", "Item Dimensions  L x W x H": "15.08 x 15.08 x 10.43 inches", "Color": "Matte Black featuring Red", "Processor Brand": "Intel", "Processor Count": "4", "Flash Memory Size": "8.0", "Hard Drive Interface": "Serial ATA", "Hard Drive Rotational Speed": "5400 RPM", "Optical Drive Type": "None", "Power Source": "AC & Battery", "Batteries": "1 Lithium ion batteries required. (included)", "ASIN": "B015PYZ0J6", "Customer Reviews": "", "Best Sellers Rank": "", "Shipping Weight": "8.8 pounds (", "Domestic Shipping": "Currently, item can be shipped only within the U.S. and to APO/FPO addresses. For APO/FPO shipments, please check with the manufacturer regarding warranty and support issues.", "International Shipping": "This item is not eligible for international shipping.", "Date First Available": "November 1, 2015", "Price": "$799.99", "Product Name": "Dell Inspiron i7559-2512BLK 15.6 Inch FHD Laptop (6th Generation Intel Core i7, 8 GB RAM, 1 TB HDD + 8 GB SSD) NVIDIA GeForce GTX 960M"},
{"Screen Size": "11.6 inches", "Max Screen Resolution": "1366 x 768 pixels", "Processor": "2.16 GHz Intel Celeron", "RAM": "2 GB DDR3L SDRAM", "Hard Drive": "16 GB flash_memory_solid_state", "Graphics Coprocessor": "Intel HD Graphics", "Chipset Brand": "intel", "Card Description": "integrated", "Wireless Type": "802.11 A/C", "Number of USB 2.0 Ports": "1", "Number of USB 3.0 Ports": "1", "Average Battery Life (in hours)": "9 hours", "Brand Name": "Acer", "Series": "CB3-131", "Item model number": "CB3-131-C3SZ", "Operating System": "Chrome", "Item Weight": "2.4 pounds", "Product Dimensions": "8 x 11.6 x 0.7 inches", "Item Dimensions  L x W x H": "8.03 x 11.57 x 0.73 inches", "Color": "Intel Celeron", "Processor Brand": "Intel", "Processor Count": "1", "Flash Memory Size": "16.0", "Batteries": "1 Lithium Polymer batteries required. (included)", "ASIN": "B019G7VPTC", "Customer Reviews": "", "Best Sellers Rank": "", "Shipping Weight": "4.2 pounds (", "Domestic Shipping": "Currently, item can be shipped only within the U.S. and to APO/FPO addresses. For APO/FPO shipments, please check with the manufacturer regarding warranty and support issues.", "International Shipping": "This item can be shipped to select countries outside of the U.S.", "Date First Available": "January 10, 2016", "Price": "$178.90", "Product Name": "Acer Chromebook CB3-131-C3SZ 11.6-Inch Laptop (Intel Celeron N2840 Dual-Core Processor,2 GB RAM,16 GB Solid State Drive,Chrome), White"},
{"Screen Size": "14 inches", "Max Screen Resolution": "1920 x 1080 pixels", "Processor": "1.6 GHz Intel Celeron", "RAM": "4 GB DDR3", "Hard Drive": "32 GB", "Graphics Coprocessor": "Intel HD Graphics", "Chipset Brand": "intel", "Card Description": "integrated", "Wireless Type": "802.11 A/C", "Number of USB 3.0 Ports": "2", "Average Battery Life (in hours)": "12 hours", "Brand Name": "Acer", "Series": "CB3-431", "Item model number": "NX.GC2AA.007", "Operating System": "Chrome", "Item Weight": "3.4 pounds", "Product Dimensions": "13.4 x 9.3 x 0.7 inches", "Item Dimensions  L x W x H": "13.43 x 9.31 x 0.67 inches", "Color": "Sparkly Silver", "Processor Brand": "Intel", "Processor Count": "1", "Flash Memory Size": "32.0", "Batteries": "1 Lithium Polymer batteries required. (included)", "ASIN": "B01CVOLVPA", "Customer Reviews": "", "Best Sellers Rank": "", "Shipping Weight": "5 pounds (", "Domestic Shipping": "Currently, item can be shipped only within the U.S. and to APO/FPO addresses. For APO/FPO shipments, please check with the manufacturer regarding warranty and support issues.", "International Shipping": "This item is not eligible for international shipping.", "Date First Available": "March 25, 2016", "Price": "$289.53", "Product Name": "Acer Chromebook 14, Aluminum, 14-inch Full HD, Intel Celeron Quad-Core N3160, 4GB LPDDR3, 32GB, Chrome, CB3-431-C5FM"},
{"Screen Size": "15.6 inches", "Screen Resolution": "1920x1080", "Max Screen Resolution": "1920x1080 pixels", "Processor": "2.3 GHz Intel Core i5", "RAM": "8 GB DDR3L SDRAM", "Memory Speed": "1600 MHz", "Hard Drive": "256 GB SSD", "Graphics Coprocessor": "NVIDIA GeForce GTX 960M 4GB GDDR5", "Chipset Brand": "Intel", "Card Description": "dedicated", "Graphics Card Ram Size": "4000 MB", "Wireless Type": "802.11 A/C", "Number of USB 3.0 Ports": "3", "Average Battery Life (in hours)": "4.5 hours", "Brand Name": "Dell", "Series": "Inspiron 15 7000 series, 7559", "Item model number": "i7559-763BLK", "Hardware Platform": "PC", "Operating System": "Windows 10", "Item Weight": "6 pounds", "Product Dimensions": "15.1 x 15.1 x 10.4 inches", "Item Dimensions  L x W x H": "15.08 x 15.08 x 10.43 inches", "Color": "Black", "Processor Brand": "Intel", "Processor Count": "4", "Computer Memory Type": "DDR3 SDRAM", "Flash Memory Size": "256", "Hard Drive Interface": "Solid State", "Optical Drive Type": "Not included", "Power Source": "AC", "Batteries": "1 Lithium ion batteries required. (included)", "ASIN": "B015PYYDMQ", "Customer Reviews": "", "Best Sellers Rank": "", "Shipping Weight": "8.8 pounds (", "Domestic Shipping": "Currently, item can be shipped only within the U.S. and to APO/FPO addresses. For APO/FPO shipments, please check with the manufacturer regarding warranty and support issues.", "International Shipping": "This item is not eligible for international shipping.", "Date First Available": "October 1, 2015", "Price": "$739.99", "Product Name": "Dell 15.6-Inch Gaming Laptop (6th Gen Intel Quad-Core i5-6300HQ Processor up to 3.2GHz, 8GB DDR3, 256GB SSD, Nvidia GeForce GTX 960M, Windows 10)"},
{"Screen Size": "13.3 inches", "Max Screen Resolution": "1920 x 1080 pixels", "Processor": "2.5 GHz None", "RAM": "8 GB DDR3 SDRAM", "Hard Drive": "flash_memory_solid_state", "Card Description": "Integrated", "Wireless Type": "802.11 A/C", "Number of USB 3.0 Ports": "2", "Brand Name": "Asus", "Series": "ZenBook", "Item model number": "UX330UA-AH54", "Operating System": "Windows 10", "Item Weight": "2.6 pounds", "Product Dimensions": "8.7 x 12.7 x 0.5 inches", "Item Dimensions  L x W x H": "8.7 x 12.7 x 0.5 inches", "Processor Brand": "Intel", "Processor Count": "2", "Batteries": "1 Lithium ion batteries required. (included)", "ASIN": "B01M18UZF5", "Customer Reviews": "", "Best Sellers Rank": "", "Shipping Weight": "4.8 pounds (", "Domestic Shipping": "Currently, item can be shipped only within the U.S. and to APO/FPO addresses. For APO/FPO shipments, please check with the manufacturer regarding warranty and support issues.", "International Shipping": "This item is not eligible for international shipping.", "Date First Available": "September 27, 2016", "Price": "$759.99", "Product Name": "ASUS  ZenBook UX330UA-AH54  13.3-inch Ultra-Slim Laptop (Core i5 Processor,  8GB DDR4, 256GB SSD, Windows 10) With Harman Kardon Quad Speakers"},
{"Screen Size": "11.6 inches", "Screen Resolution": "1366 x 768 pixels", "Max Screen Resolution": "1366*768 pixels", "Processor": "1.8 GHz AMD A Series", "RAM": "4 GB DDR3", "Hard Drive": "SSD", "Chipset Brand": "ARM Mali", "Card Description": "Mali-T764", "Wireless Type": "802.11 A/C", "Brand Name": "Asus", "Series": "Chromebook C201PA", "Item model number": "C201PA-DS02", "Hardware Platform": "PC", "Operating System": "Chrome", "Item Weight": "2 pounds", "Product Dimensions": "11.3 x 7.6 x 0.7 inches", "Item Dimensions  L x W x H": "11.3 x 7.64 x 0.7 inches", "Color": "Navy Blue", "Processor Brand": "Rockchip", "Processor Count": "4", "Computer Memory Type": "DDR3 SDRAM", "Flash Memory Size": "16", "Optical Drive Type": "None", "Audio-out Ports (#)": "1", "Battery Type": "Lithium Polymer (LiPo)", "Power Source": "Battery", "Voltage": "19 volts", "Batteries": "1 Lithium ion batteries required. (included)", "ASIN": "B00VUV0MG0", "Customer Reviews": "", "Best Sellers Rank": "", "Shipping Weight": "3.4 pounds (", "Domestic Shipping": "Currently, item can be shipped only within the U.S. and to APO/FPO addresses. For APO/FPO shipments, please check with the manufacturer regarding warranty and support issues.", "International Shipping": "This item is not eligible for international shipping.", "Date First Available": "April 8, 2015", "Price": "$159.00", "Product Name": "ASUS C201PA-DS02 11.6 inch Chromebook (1.8GHz Quad-Core, 4GB LPDDR3, 16GB SSD), Navy Blue"},
{"Screen Size": "15.6 inches", "Max Screen Resolution": "1920 x 1080 pixels", "Processor": "1.5 GHz Intel Celeron", "RAM": "4 GB DDR3L SDRAM", "Hard Drive": "16 GB flash_memory_solid_state", "Graphics Coprocessor": "Intel HD Graphics", "Chipset Brand": "intel", "Card Description": "integrated", "Wireless Type": "802.11 A/C", "Number of USB 3.0 Ports": "1", "Average Battery Life (in hours)": "9 hours", "Brand Name": "Acer", "Series": "CB5-571", "Item model number": "CB5-571-C1DZ", "Operating System": "Chrome", "Item Weight": "4.8 pounds", "Product Dimensions": "15.1 x 9.7 x 1 inches", "Item Dimensions  L x W x H": "15.08 x 9.65 x 0.97 inches", "Color": "Linen White", "Processor Brand": "Intel", "Processor Count": "1", "Flash Memory Size": "16.0", "Batteries": "1 Lithium ion batteries required. (included)", "ASIN": "B00TU7U4PU", "Customer Reviews": "", "Best Sellers Rank": "", "Shipping Weight": "6.3 pounds (", "Domestic Shipping": "Currently, item can be shipped only within the U.S. and to APO/FPO addresses. For APO/FPO shipments, please check with the manufacturer regarding warranty and support issues.", "International Shipping": "This item can be shipped to select countries outside of the U.S.", "Date First Available": "March 18, 2015", "Price": "$249.00", "Product Name": "Acer Chromebook 15 CB5-571-C1DZ (15.6-Inch Full HD IPS, 4GB RAM, 16GB SSD)"},
{"Screen Size": "15.6 inches", "Screen Resolution": "1920 x 1080 pixels", "Max Screen Resolution": "1920x1080 pixels", "Processor": "2.3 GHz Intel Core i5", "RAM": "8 GB DDR3L SDRAM", "Memory Speed": "1600 MHz", "Hard Drive": "128 GB flash_memory_solid_state", "Graphics Coprocessor": "shared", "Chipset Brand": "intel", "Card Description": "integrated", "Wireless Type": "802.11 A/C", "Number of USB 2.0 Ports": "2", "Number of USB 3.0 Ports": "1", "Brand Name": "HP", "Series": "Notebook", "Item model number": "W2M74UA#ABA", "Hardware Platform": "PC", "Operating System": "Windows 10", "Item Weight": "4.7 pounds", "Product Dimensions": "10 x 15.1 x 0.9 inches", "Item Dimensions  L x W x H": "10.02 x 15.12 x 0.95 inches", "Color": "Silver", "Processor Brand": "Intel", "Processor Count": "2", "Computer Memory Type": "DDR3 SDRAM", "Flash Memory Size": "128", "Optical Drive Type": "DVD+RW", "Audio-out Ports (#)": "1", "Battery Type": "Lithium-Ion (Li-Ion)", "Voltage": "19 volts", "Batteries": "1 Lithium ion batteries required. (included)", "ASIN": "B01CGGOZOW", "Customer Reviews": "", "Best Sellers Rank": "", "Shipping Weight": "6 pounds (", "Domestic Shipping": "Currently, item can be shipped only within the U.S. and to APO/FPO addresses. For APO/FPO shipments, please check with the manufacturer regarding warranty and support issues.", "International Shipping": "This item is not eligible for international shipping.", "Date First Available": "April 10, 2016", "Price": "$495.00", "Product Name": "HP 15-ay013nr 15.6\" Full-HD Laptop (6th Generation Core i5, 8GB RAM, 128GB SSD) with Windows 10"},
{"Screen Size": "15.6 inches", "Max Screen Resolution": "1366x768 pixels", "Processor": "2.3 GHz Intel Core i3", "RAM": "4 GB DDR3 SDRAM", "Hard Drive": "1 TB mechanical_hard_drive", "Card Description": "Integrated", "Wireless Type": "802.11 A/C", "Number of USB 3.0 Ports": "1", "Average Battery Life (in hours)": "6.5 hours", "Brand Name": "Acer", "Series": "ES1-572", "Item model number": "ES1-572-31KW", "Operating System": "Windows 10", "Item Weight": "5.3 pounds", "Product Dimensions": "10.2 x 15 x 1 inches", "Item Dimensions  L x W x H": "10.16 x 15.03 x 0.97 inches", "Color": "Midnight Black", "Processor Brand": "Intel", "Processor Count": "1", "Computer Memory Type": "DDR3 SDRAM", "Hard Drive Rotational Speed": "5400 RPM", "Batteries": "1 Lithium ion batteries required. (included)", "ASIN": "B01J42JPL4", "Customer Reviews": "", "Best Sellers Rank": "", "Shipping Weight": "6.7 pounds (", "Domestic Shipping": "Currently, item can be shipped only within the U.S. and to APO/FPO addresses. For APO/FPO shipments, please check with the manufacturer regarding warranty and support issues.", "International Shipping": "This item is not eligible for international shipping.", "Date First Available": "August 14, 2016", "Price": "$319.99", "Product Name": "Acer Aspire ES 15, 15.6\" HD, Intel Core i3-6100U, 4GB DDR3L, 1TB HDD, Windows 10 Home, ES1-572-31KW"},
{"Screen Size": "13.3 inches", "Screen Resolution": "1280 x 800 pixels", "Max Screen Resolution": "1280x800", "Processor": "2.5 GHz Intel Core i5", "RAM": "4 GB DDR3-SDRAM", "Memory Speed": "1600 MHz", "Hard Drive": "500 GB SATA 2.5 HARD DRIVE", "Graphics Coprocessor": "integrated_graphics", "Chipset Brand": "Intel", "Card Description": "integrated", "Wireless Type": "802.11A, 802.11B, 802.11G, 802.11n", "Average Battery Life (in hours)": "8 hours", "Brand Name": "Apple", "Series": "MD761", "Item model number": "MD101", "Hardware Platform": "Mac", "Operating System": "Mac OS X 10.7 Lion", "Item Weight": "4.5 pounds", "Product Dimensions": "12.8 x 0.3 x 0.9 inches", "Item Dimensions  L x W x H": "12.8 x 0.35 x 0.95 inches", "Color": "Silver", "Processor Brand": "Intel", "Processor Count": "2", "Computer Memory Type": "DDR3 SDRAM", "Hard Drive Interface": "Serial ATA", "Hard Drive Rotational Speed": "5400 RPM", "Optical Drive Type": "DVD Super Multi DL", "Audio-out Ports (#)": "1", "Battery Type": "Lithium Polymer (LiPo)", "Batteries": "1 Lithium ion batteries required. (included)", "ASIN": "B008BEYEL8", "Customer Reviews": "", "Best Sellers Rank": "", "Shipping Weight": "8.2 pounds (", "Domestic Shipping": "Currently, item can be shipped only within the U.S. and to APO/FPO addresses. For APO/FPO shipments, please check with the manufacturer regarding warranty and support issues.", "International Shipping": "This item is not eligible for international shipping.", "Date First Available": "January 17, 2013", "Price": "$918.02", "Product Name": "Apple 13 \" MacBook Pro / MD101LL/A / 2.5GHz Intel Core i5, 4GB RAM, 500GB HDD"},
{"Screen Size": "15.6 inches", "Max Screen Resolution": "1920*1080 pixels", "Processor": "2.5 GHz Intel Core i7", "RAM": "8 GB DDR4 SDRAM", "Hard Drive": "512 GB flash_memory_solid_state", "Graphics Coprocessor": "geforce gtx 960m", "Chipset Brand": "nvidia", "Card Description": "Integrated", "Wireless Type": "802.11 A/C", "Number of USB 3.0 Ports": "2", "Brand Name": "Asus", "Series": "K501UW", "Item model number": "K501UW-AB78", "Operating System": "Windows 10 (64bit)", "Item Weight": "4.4 pounds", "Product Dimensions": "15.6 x 10 x 0.8 inches", "Item Dimensions  L x W x H": "15.6 x 10 x 0.8 inches", "Processor Brand": "Intel", "Processor Count": "2", "Computer Memory Type": "DDR SDRAM", "Flash Memory Size": "512.0", "Batteries": "1 Lithium ion batteries required. (included)", "ASIN": "B01DT49XN8", "Customer Reviews": "", "Best Sellers Rank": "", "Shipping Weight": "7.4 pounds (", "Domestic Shipping": "Currently, item can be shipped only within the U.S. and to APO/FPO addresses. For APO/FPO shipments, please check with the manufacturer regarding warranty and support issues.", "International Shipping": "This item is not eligible for international shipping.", "Date First Available": "March 31, 2016", "Price": "$869.99", "Product Name": "ASUS K501UW-AB78 15.6-inch Full-HD Gaming Laptop (Intel Core i7, GTX 960M, 8GB DDR4, 512GB SSD) Glacier Grey"},
{"Screen Size": "11.6 inches", "Max Screen Resolution": "1366 x 768 pixels", "Processor": "1.6 GHz Intel Celeron", "RAM": "4 GB DDR3 SDRAM", "Memory Speed": "1600 MHz", "Hard Drive": "32 GB emmc", "Card Description": "Integrated", "Wireless Type": "802.11 A/C", "Number of USB 2.0 Ports": "1", "Number of USB 3.0 Ports": "1", "Brand Name": "HP", "Series": "Stream", "Item model number": "11-y010nr", "Operating System": "Windows 10", "Item Weight": "2.6 pounds", "Product Dimensions": "8.1 x 11.8 x 0.7 inches", "Item Dimensions  L x W x H": "8.1 x 11.8 x 0.71 inches", "Color": "Aqua Blue", "Processor Brand": "Intel", "Processor Count": "2", "Flash Memory Size": "32", "Batteries": "1 Lithium ion batteries required. (included)", "ASIN": "B01JLCKP48", "Customer Reviews": "", "Best Sellers Rank": "", "Shipping Weight": "3.8 pounds (", "Domestic Shipping": "Currently, item can be shipped only within the U.S. and to APO/FPO addresses. For APO/FPO shipments, please check with the manufacturer regarding warranty and support issues.", "International Shipping": "This item is not eligible for international shipping.", "Date First Available": "September 1, 2016", "Price": "$199.99", "Product Name": "HP Stream Laptop PC 11-y010nr (Intel Celeron N3060, 4 GB RAM, 32 GB eMMC) with Office 365 Personal for one year"},
{"Screen Size": "15.6 inches", "Max Screen Resolution": "1920x1080 pixels", "Processor": "2.6 GHz Intel Core i7", "RAM": "16 GB", "Memory Speed": "2133 MHz", "Hard Drive": "1 TB flash_memory_solid_state", "Graphics Coprocessor": "geforce", "Card Description": "Dedicated", "Wireless Type": "802.11 A/C", "Number of USB 3.0 Ports": "3", "Average Battery Life (in hours)": "5 hours", "Brand Name": "Asus", "Series": "Republic of Gamers", "Item model number": "GL502VS-DB71", "Operating System": "Windows 10", "Item Weight": "4.9 pounds", "Product Dimensions": "15.4 x 10.5 x 1.2 inches", "Item Dimensions  L x W x H": "15.4 x 10.5 x 1.2 inches", "Color": "ROG Metallic", "Processor Brand": "Intel", "Processor Count": "4", "Computer Memory Type": "GDDR5", "Hard Drive Rotational Speed": "7200 RPM", "Voltage": "19.5 volts", "Batteries": "1 Lithium ion batteries required. (included)", "ASIN": "B01K1INYD0", "Customer Reviews": "", "Best Sellers Rank": "", "Shipping Weight": "9.8 pounds (", "Domestic Shipping": "Currently, item can be shipped only within the U.S. and to APO/FPO addresses. For APO/FPO shipments, please check with the manufacturer regarding warranty and support issues.", "International Shipping": "This item is not eligible for international shipping.", "Date First Available": "August 9, 2016", "Price": "$1,598.00", "Product Name": "ASUS ROG GL502VS-DB71 15.6\" Full\u00adHD Gaming Laptop,Intel Core i7\u00ad6700HQ,NVIDIA GTX 1070,256GB PCIE SSD+1TB HDD,Windows 10,Black"},
{"Screen Size": "10.1 inches", "Screen Resolution": "1280 x 800 pixels", "Max Screen Resolution": "1280 x 800 pixels", "Processor": "1.4 GHz Atom Z8500", "RAM": "4 GB DDR3", "Memory Speed": "1600 MHz", "Hard Drive": "64 GB Flash Memory Solid State", "Graphics Coprocessor": "Intel HD", "Card Description": "integrated", "Wireless Type": "54g", "Brand Name": "Asus", "Series": "ASUS", "Item model number": "T100HA-C4-GR", "Operating System": "Windows 10", "Item Weight": "1.7 pounds", "Product Dimensions": "6.7 x 10.2 x 0.5 inches", "Item Dimensions  L x W x H": "6.7 x 10.2 x 0.5 inches", "Color": "Gray", "Rear Webcam Resolution": "5 \tMP", "Processor Brand": "Intel", "Processor Count": "4", "Computer Memory Type": "DDR3 SDRAM", "Flash Memory Size": "128.0", "Optical Drive Type": "None", "Audio-out Ports (#)": "1", "Battery Type": "Lithium Polymer (LiPo)", "Batteries": "1 Lithium Polymer batteries required. (included)", "ASIN": "B014854RGK", "Customer Reviews": "", "Best Sellers Rank": "", "Shipping Weight": "3.2 pounds (", "Domestic Shipping": "Currently, item can be shipped only within the U.S. and to APO/FPO addresses. For APO/FPO shipments, please check with the manufacturer regarding warranty and support issues.", "International Shipping": "This item can be shipped to select countries outside of the U.S.", "Date First Available": "October 8, 2015", "Price": "$299.00", "Product Name": "ASUS Transformer Book T100HA-C4-GR 10.1-Inch 2 in 1 Touchscreen Laptop (Cherry Trail Quad-Core Z8500 Processor, 4GB RAM, 64GB Storage, Windows 10), Gray"},
{"Screen Size": "15.6 inches", "Screen Resolution": "1366x768", "Max Screen Resolution": "1366 x 768 HD TouchScreen", "Processor": "2.2 GHz Intel Core i5", "RAM": "8 GB SDRAM DDR3", "Hard Drive": "1 TB HDD 5400 rpm", "Graphics Coprocessor": "integrated_graphics", "Chipset Brand": "intel", "Card Description": "integrated", "Wireless Type": "802.11A, 802.11bgn, Bluetooth", "Number of USB 2.0 Ports": "1", "Average Battery Life (in hours)": "5 hours", "Brand Name": "Dell", "Series": "Dell Touch 15", "Item model number": "Dell 15", "Hardware Platform": "PC", "Operating System": "Windows 10", "Item Weight": "4.8 pounds", "Product Dimensions": "15 x 10 x 0.9 inches", "Item Dimensions  L x W x H": "15 x 10 x 0.87 inches", "Color": "Black", "Processor Brand": "Intel\u00ae CoreTM i5-5200U", "Processor Count": "2", "Computer Memory Type": "DDR3 SDRAM", "Hard Drive Interface": "Serial ATA", "Hard Drive Rotational Speed": "5400 RPM", "Power Source": "AC & Battery", "Batteries": "1 Lithium ion batteries required.", "ASIN": "B01MRKWB5K", "Customer Reviews": "", "Best Sellers Rank": "", "Shipping Weight": "7.1 pounds (", "Date First Available": "November 5, 2016", "Price": "$446.00", "Product Name": "Dell Inspiron 15.6\u201d Touchscreen HD I3558-5501BLK Laptop (2017 Newest Model), Intel Core i5-5200U Processor, 8GB Memory, 1TB HDD, HDMI, Bluetooth, DVD-RW, WiFi, HD Webcam, Windows 10 -MaxxAudio"},
{"Screen Size": "15.6 inches", "Max Screen Resolution": "1920 x 1080 pixels", "Processor": "2.3 GHz None", "RAM": "4 GB", "Hard Drive": "1000 GB mechanical_hard_drive", "Card Description": "Integrated", "Wireless Type": "802.11 A/C", "Number of USB 3.0 Ports": "1", "Brand Name": "Asus", "Series": "VivoBook", "Item model number": "F556UA-AB32", "Operating System": "Windows 10", "Item Weight": "5.1 pounds", "Product Dimensions": "10.1 x 15 x 1 inches", "Item Dimensions  L x W x H": "10.1 x 15 x 1 inches", "Processor Brand": "Intel", "Processor Count": "2", "Computer Memory Type": "DDR4 SDRAM", "Hard Drive Rotational Speed": "5400 RPM", "Batteries": "1 Lithium ion batteries required. (included)", "ASIN": "B01LX0KIGB", "Customer Reviews": "", "Best Sellers Rank": "", "Shipping Weight": "6.7 pounds (", "Domestic Shipping": "Currently, item can be shipped only within the U.S. and to APO/FPO addresses. For APO/FPO shipments, please check with the manufacturer regarding warranty and support issues.", "International Shipping": "This item is not eligible for international shipping.", "Date First Available": "September 27, 2016", "Price": "$364.99", "Product Name": "ASUS F556UA-AB32 15.6-inch Full-HD Laptop, Core i3, 4GB RAM, 1TB HDD with Windows 10"},
{"Screen Size": "15.6 inches", "Max Screen Resolution": "1920*1080 pixels", "Processor": "2.5 GHz Core i5-5287U", "RAM": "8 GB", "Hard Drive": "256 GB Flash Memory Solid State", "Chipset Brand": "Intel", "Card Description": "Dedicated", "Number of USB 2.0 Ports": "1", "Number of USB 3.0 Ports": "1", "Brand Name": "Asus", "Series": "F556UA-AB54", "Item model number": "F556UA-AB54", "Operating System": "Windows 10", "Item Weight": "5.1 pounds", "Product Dimensions": "15 x 1 x 10.1 inches", "Item Dimensions  L x W x H": "15 x 1 x 10.1 inches", "Color": "Gold", "Processor Brand": "Intel", "Processor Count": "4", "Flash Memory Size": "256.0", "Optical Drive Type": "DVD+RW", "Batteries": "1 Lithium Polymer batteries required. (included)", "ASIN": "B01M08DL26", "Customer Reviews": "", "Best Sellers Rank": "", "Shipping Weight": "6.7 pounds (", "Domestic Shipping": "Currently, item can be shipped only within the U.S. and to APO/FPO addresses. For APO/FPO shipments, please check with the manufacturer regarding warranty and support issues.", "International Shipping": "This item is not eligible for international shipping.", "Date First Available": "September 15, 2016", "Price": "$549.00", "Product Name": "ASUS F556UA-AB54 NB 15.6\" FHD Intel Core i5 8GB 256G SSD Windows 10 Laptop (Gold)"},
{"Screen Size": "15.6 inches", "Screen Resolution": "1366x768", "Max Screen Resolution": "1366 x 768 (HD)", "Processor": "4.6 GHz Intel Core i3", "RAM": "4 GB SDRAM DDR3", "Hard Drive": "500 GB HDD 5400 rpm", "Graphics Coprocessor": "Intel Integrated Graphics", "Chipset Brand": "intel", "Card Description": "integrated", "Wireless Type": "802.11bgn, Bluetooth", "Number of USB 2.0 Ports": "1", "Average Battery Life (in hours)": "5 hours", "Brand Name": "Asus", "Series": "Asus X Series", "Item model number": "Asus VivoBook", "Hardware Platform": "PC", "Operating System": "Windows 10", "Item Weight": "4.5 pounds", "Product Dimensions": "15 x 9.9 x 1 inches", "Item Dimensions  L x W x H": "15 x 9.92 x 1 inches", "Color": "Silver", "Processor Brand": "Pentium N3700", "Processor Count": "4", "Computer Memory Type": "DDR3 SDRAM", "Hard Drive Interface": "Serial ATA", "Hard Drive Rotational Speed": "5400 RPM", "Power Source": "AC & Battery", "Voltage": "19 volts", "Batteries": "1 Lithium Metal batteries required.", "ASIN": "B01KAP7RJG", "Customer Reviews": "", "Best Sellers Rank": "", "Shipping Weight": "6 pounds (", "Date First Available": "June 17, 2016", "Price": "$268.00", "Product Name": "ASUS VivoBook X540SA 15.6-Inch High Performance Premium HD Laptop (Intel Quad Core Pentium N3700 Processor up to 2.4 GHz, 4 GB RAM, 500GB HDD, Windows 10) Silver"},
{"Screen Size": "12 inches", "Max Screen Resolution": "1920x1280 pixels", "Processor": "0.9 GHz Core M 6Y30", "RAM": "4 GB DDR3 SDRAM", "Hard Drive": "flash_memory_solid_state", "Card Description": "Integrated", "Graphics Card Ram Size": "2095 MB", "Wireless Type": "802.11 A/C", "Number of USB 3.0 Ports": "1", "Brand Name": "HP", "Series": "Spectre 12-a008nr x2 Detachable Laptop", "Item model number": "N5S21UA#ABA", "Operating System": "Windows 10", "Item Weight": "2.7 pounds", "Product Dimensions": "8.2 x 11.8 x 0.5 inches", "Item Dimensions  L x W x H": "8.23 x 11.81 x 0.52 inches", "Rear Webcam Resolution": "8 \tMP", "Processor Brand": "Intel", "Processor Count": "2", "Flash Memory Size": "128.0", "Optical Drive Type": "None", "Batteries": "1 Lithium ion batteries required. (included)", "ASIN": "B01GFDHK4E", "Customer Reviews": "", "Best Sellers Rank": "", "Shipping Weight": "7.8 pounds (", "Domestic Shipping": "Currently, item can be shipped only within the U.S. and to APO/FPO addresses. For APO/FPO shipments, please check with the manufacturer regarding warranty and support issues.", "International Shipping": "This item is not eligible for international shipping.", "Date First Available": "July 11, 2016", "Price": "$399.88", "Product Name": "HP Spectre X2 12-a008nr (Intel Core M3, 4GB RAM, 128GB SSD, Touch Screen) with Windows 10"},
{"Screen Size": "13.3 inches", "Max Screen Resolution": "1440x900", "Processor": "1.6 GHz Intel Core i5", "RAM": "8 GB DDR3 SDRAM", "Hard Drive": "128 GB", "Graphics Coprocessor": "integrated_graphics", "Chipset Brand": "intel", "Card Description": "integrated", "Wireless Type": "802.11abg, 802.11 A/C, 802.11 a/b/g/n, 802.11A", "Brand Name": "Apple", "Series": "MacBook Air 13", "Hardware Platform": "Mac", "Operating System": "Mac OS X", "Item Weight": "3 pounds", "Product Dimensions": "8.9 x 12.8 x 0.7 inches", "Item Dimensions  L x W x H": "8.94 x 12.8 x 0.68 inches", "Processor Brand": "Intel", "Processor Count": "1", "Computer Memory Type": "DDR3 SDRAM", "Hard Drive Interface": "Solid State", "ASIN": "B015WXL0C6", "Customer Reviews": "", "Best Sellers Rank": "", "Shipping Weight": "4.8 pounds (", "Date First Available": "September 28, 2015", "Price": "$929.29", "Product Name": "Apple MacBook Air 13.3-Inch Laptop (Intel Core i5 1.6GHz, 128GB Flash, 8GB RAM, OS X El Capitan)"},
{"Screen Size": "11.6 inches", "Screen Resolution": "1366 x 768 pixels", "Max Screen Resolution": "1366 x 768 pixels", "Processor": "2.16 GHz Intel Celeron", "RAM": "2 GB DDR3", "Hard Drive": "16 GB SSD", "Graphics Coprocessor": "integrated_graphics", "Chipset Brand": "Intel HD Graphics", "Card Description": "Integrated", "Wireless Type": "802.11 A/C", "Number of USB 2.0 Ports": "1", "Number of USB 3.0 Ports": "1", "Average Battery Life (in hours)": "11 hours", "Brand Name": "Samsung", "Series": "Chromebook 3", "Item model number": "XE500C13-K01US", "Hardware Platform": "PC", "Operating System": "Chrome", "Item Weight": "2.5 pounds", "Product Dimensions": "11.4 x 8 x 0.7 inches", "Item Dimensions  L x W x H": "11.37 x 8.04 x 0.7 inches", "Color": "Black", "Processor Brand": "Intel", "Processor Count": "2", "Computer Memory Type": "DDR3 SDRAM", "Flash Memory Size": "16", "Hard Drive Rotational Speed": "1 RPM", "Optical Drive Type": "None", "Audio-out Ports (#)": "1", "Battery Type": "Lithium-Ion (Li-Ion)", "Batteries": "Lithium Metal batteries required. (included)", "ASIN": "B01APA6K6M", "Customer Reviews": "", "Best Sellers Rank": "", "Shipping Weight": "3.7 pounds (", "Domestic Shipping": "Currently, item can be shipped only within the U.S. and to APO/FPO addresses. For APO/FPO shipments, please check with the manufacturer regarding warranty and support issues.", "International Shipping": "This item is not eligible for international shipping.", "Date First Available": "February 15, 2016", "Price": "$164.00", "Product Name": "Samsung Chromebook 3 XE500C13-K01US 2 GB RAM 16GB SSD 11.6\" Laptop"},
{"Screen Size": "11.6 inches", "Max Screen Resolution": "1366x768 pixels", "Processor": "1.6 GHz Intel Celeron", "RAM": "4 GB DDR3 SDRAM", "Chipset Brand": "intel", "Card Description": "Integrated", "Wireless Type": "802.11 A/C", "Number of USB 3.0 Ports": "1", "Average Battery Life (in hours)": "10 hours", "Brand Name": "Acer", "Series": "CB5-132T", "Item model number": "CB5-132T-C1LK", "Operating System": "Chrome", "Item Weight": "2.8 pounds", "Product Dimensions": "8 x 11.6 x 0.8 inches", "Item Dimensions  L x W x H": "8.03 x 11.57 x 0.76 inches", "Color": "Intel Celeron", "Processor Brand": "Intel", "Processor Count": "1", "Flash Memory Size": "32.0", "Batteries": "1 Lithium ion batteries required. (included)", "ASIN": "B01J42JPJG", "Customer Reviews": "", "Best Sellers Rank": "", "Shipping Weight": "4.2 pounds (", "Domestic Shipping": "Currently, item can be shipped only within the U.S. and to APO/FPO addresses. For APO/FPO shipments, please check with the manufacturer regarding warranty and support issues.", "International Shipping": "This item can be shipped to select countries outside of the U.S.", "Date First Available": "August 21, 2016", "Price": "$269.99", "Product Name": "Acer Chromebook R 11 Convertible, 11.6-Inch HD Touch, Intel Celeron N3150, 4GB DDR3L, 32GB, Chrome, CB5-132T-C1LK"},
{"Screen Size": "17.3 inches", "Max Screen Resolution": "1366 X 768", "Processor": "2.2 GHz Intel Core i5", "RAM": "8 GB SDRAM DDR3", "Memory Speed": "1600 MHz", "Hard Drive": "1 TB HDD 5400 rpm", "Graphics Coprocessor": "integrated_graphics", "Chipset Brand": "intel", "Card Description": "integrated", "Wireless Type": "Bluetooth", "Number of USB 2.0 Ports": "2", "Average Battery Life (in hours)": "6 hours", "Brand Name": "Dell", "Series": "Dell Inspiron", "Item model number": "Dell Inspiron", "Hardware Platform": "PC", "Operating System": "Windows 10", "Item Weight": "4.8 pounds", "Product Dimensions": "15 x 10 x 0.9 inches", "Item Dimensions  L x W x H": "15 x 10 x 0.9 inches", "Color": "Black", "Processor Brand": "Intel", "Processor Count": "1", "Computer Memory Type": "DDR3 SDRAM", "Hard Drive Interface": "Serial ATA", "Hard Drive Rotational Speed": "5400 RPM", "Power Source": "AC & Battery", "ASIN": "B01MXLQ5TM", "Customer Reviews": "", "Best Sellers Rank": "", "Shipping Weight": "7 pounds (", "Date First Available": "November 14, 2016", "Price": "$454.49", "Product Name": "2017 Newest Dell Inspiron 15.6 inch Touchscreen HD Premium Laptop, Intel Core i5-5200U Processor 2.2GHz, 8GB RAM, 1TB HDD, HDMI, Bluetooth, DVD-RW, 802.11ac, HD Webcam, Windows 10 -MaxxAudio"},
{"Screen Size": "13.3 inches", "Screen Resolution": "1920x1080", "Max Screen Resolution": "1920X1080 pixels", "Processor": "3.1 GHz Intel Core i5", "RAM": "8 GB", "Memory Speed": "2400 GHz", "Hard Drive": "1000 GB SATA", "Graphics Coprocessor": "integrated_graphics", "Chipset Brand": "Intel HD Graphic 620", "Card Description": "Intel HD Graphics 620", "Wireless Type": "802.11 A/C", "Number of USB 2.0 Ports": "1", "Number of USB 3.0 Ports": "2", "Brand Name": "Dell", "Series": "Inspiron 13 5000 Series (5378)", "Item model number": "i5378-2885GRY", "Hardware Platform": "PC", "Operating System": "Windows 10", "Item Weight": "3.4 pounds", "Product Dimensions": "8.8 x 12.8 x 0.8 inches", "Item Dimensions  L x W x H": "8.85 x 12.75 x 0.76 inches", "Color": "Theoretical Gray", "Processor Brand": "Intel", "Processor Count": "2", "Computer Memory Type": "SDRAM", "Hard Drive Interface": "eSATA", "Hard Drive Rotational Speed": "5400 RPM", "Optical Drive Type": "None", "Power Source": "AC & Battery", "Batteries": "1 Lithium ion batteries required. (included)", "ASIN": "B01L8PDMO6", "Customer Reviews": "", "Best Sellers Rank": "", "Shipping Weight": "5.5 pounds (", "Domestic Shipping": "Currently, item can be shipped only within the U.S. and to APO/FPO addresses. For APO/FPO shipments, please check with the manufacturer regarding warranty and support issues.", "International Shipping": "This item is not eligible for international shipping.", "Date First Available": "September 12, 2016", "Price": "$515.00", "Product Name": "Dell Inspiron i5378-2885GRY 13.3\" FHD 2-in-1 Laptop (7th Generation Intel Core i5, 8GB RAM, 1TB HDD) Microsoft Signature Image"},
{"Screen Size": "13.5 inches", "Max Screen Resolution": "3000*2000 pixels", "Processor": "2.6 GHz Core M Family", "RAM": "16 GB LPDDR3", "Hard Drive": "512 GB flash_memory_solid_state", "Graphics Coprocessor": "Nvidia GeForce GPU", "Card Description": "dedicated", "Wireless Type": "802.11 A/C", "Number of USB 3.0 Ports": "2", "Brand Name": "Microsoft", "Series": "CR7-00001", "Item model number": "CR7-00001", "Hardware Platform": "PC", "Operating System": "Windows 10 Pro", "Item Weight": "3.5 pounds", "Product Dimensions": "10.9 x 16.5 x 1.9 inches", "Item Dimensions  L x W x H": "10.95 x 16.46 x 1.93 inches", "Color": "Silver", "Rear Webcam Resolution": "2048 \tMP", "Processor Brand": "Intel", "Processor Count": "2", "Flash Memory Size": "512.0", "Batteries": "1 Lithium ion batteries required. (included)", "ASIN": "B0163GNS5S", "Customer Reviews": "", "Best Sellers Rank": "", "Shipping Weight": "7.8 pounds (", "Domestic Shipping": "Currently, item can be shipped only within the U.S. and to APO/FPO addresses. For APO/FPO shipments, please check with the manufacturer regarding warranty and support issues.", "International Shipping": "This item is not eligible for international shipping.", "Date First Available": "October 6, 2015", "Price": "$2,150.00", "Product Name": "Microsoft Surface Book (512 GB, 16 GB RAM, Intel Core i7, NVIDIA GeForce graphics)"},
{"Screen Size": "11.6 inches", "Max Screen Resolution": "1366 x 768 pixels", "Processor": "1.6 GHz Celeron N3050", "RAM": "4 GB DDR3 SDRAM", "Hard Drive": "emmc", "Card Description": "Integrated", "Wireless Type": "802.11 A/C", "Number of USB 3.0 Ports": "1", "Brand Name": "HP", "Series": "Stream", "Item model number": "11-y020nr", "Operating System": "Windows 10", "Item Weight": "2.6 pounds", "Product Dimensions": "8.1 x 11.8 x 0.7 inches", "Item Dimensions  L x W x H": "8.1 x 11.8 x 0.71 inches", "Color": "Violet/Purple", "Processor Brand": "Intel", "Processor Count": "2", "Flash Memory Size": "32.0", "Batteries": "1 Lithium ion batteries required. (included)", "ASIN": "B01JLCKPAC", "Customer Reviews": "", "Best Sellers Rank": "", "Shipping Weight": "3.7 pounds (", "Domestic Shipping": "Currently, item can be shipped only within the U.S. and to APO/FPO addresses. For APO/FPO shipments, please check with the manufacturer regarding warranty and support issues.", "International Shipping": "This item is not eligible for international shipping.", "Date First Available": "September 1, 2016", "Price": "$217.72", "Product Name": "HP Stream Laptop PC 11-y020nr (Intel Celeron N3060, 4 GB RAM, 32 GB eMMC) with Office 365 Personal for one year"},
{"Screen Size": "17.3 inches", "Max Screen Resolution": "1920 x 1080 pixels", "Processor": "2.6 GHz Intel Core i7", "RAM": "16 GB", "Hard Drive": "1 TB mechanical_hard_drive", "Chipset Brand": "NVIDIA", "Card Description": "Dedicated", "Wireless Type": "802.11 A/C", "Number of USB 3.0 Ports": "3", "Brand Name": "Asus", "Series": "ROG", "Item model number": "GL702VM-DB71", "Operating System": "Windows 10", "Item Weight": "6 pounds", "Product Dimensions": "10.8 x 16.5 x 0.9 inches", "Item Dimensions  L x W x H": "10.8 x 16.5 x 0.9 inches", "Processor Brand": "Intel", "Processor Count": "4", "Hard Drive Rotational Speed": "7200 RPM", "Batteries": "1 Lithium ion batteries required. (included)", "ASIN": "B01KB0W4R0", "Customer Reviews": "", "Best Sellers Rank": "", "Shipping Weight": "10.1 pounds (", "Domestic Shipping": "Currently, item can be shipped only within the U.S. and to APO/FPO addresses. For APO/FPO shipments, please check with the manufacturer regarding warranty and support issues.", "International Shipping": "This item is not eligible for international shipping.", "Date First Available": "August 26, 2016", "Price": "$1,366.36", "Product Name": "Asus ROG Strix GL702VM-DB71 17.3-Inch. G-SYNC VR Ready Thin and Light Gaming Laptop (NVIDIA GTX 1060 6GB Intel Core i7-6700HQ 16GB DDR4 1TB 7200RPM HDD)"},
{"Screen Size": "15.6 inches", "Max Screen Resolution": "1920 x 1080 (1080P Full HD)", "Processor": "2.3 GHz Intel Core i5", "RAM": "8 GB DDR3 SDRAM", "Hard Drive": "1 TB mechanical_hard_drive", "Graphics Coprocessor": "integrated_graphics", "Chipset Brand": "intel", "Card Description": "integrated", "Wireless Type": "802.11A, 802.11bgn, Bluetooth", "Brand Name": "Dell", "Series": "Dell Inspiron 15 5000 Series", "Item model number": "8.84116E+11", "Hardware Platform": "PC", "Operating System": "Windows 10", "Item Weight": "5.4 pounds", "Product Dimensions": "15 x 10.2 x 0.9 inches", "Item Dimensions  L x W x H": "15 x 10.25 x 0.94 inches", "Color": "Silver", "Processor Brand": "Intel Core i5-6200U", "Processor Count": "2", "Computer Memory Type": "DDR3 SDRAM", "Hard Drive Interface": "Serial ATA", "Hard Drive Rotational Speed": "5400 RPM", "Power Source": "AC & Battery", "ASIN": "B01EXQHRMK", "Customer Reviews": "", "Best Sellers Rank": "", "Shipping Weight": "7.7 pounds (", "Date First Available": "April 28, 2016", "Price": "$439.00", "Product Name": "2016 Newest Dell Inspiron 15 5000 15.6\" FHD Touchscreen Laptop, Intel Core i5-6200U, 8 GB RAM, 1 TB HDD, DVD, Backlit keyboard, HDMI, Bluetooth, 802.11ac, RealSense 3D Webcam, Windows 10-MaxxAudio Pro"},
{"Screen Size": "15.6 inches", "Max Screen Resolution": "1920 x 1080 pixels", "Processor": "2.5 GHz Intel Core i7", "RAM": "8 GB", "Hard Drive": "256 GB flash_memory_solid_state", "Graphics Coprocessor": "geforce", "Chipset Brand": "NVIDIA GeForce 940MX", "Card Description": "Dedicated", "Graphics Card Ram Size": "2000 MB", "Wireless Type": "802.11 A/C", "Number of USB 3.0 Ports": "2", "Average Battery Life (in hours)": "12 hours", "Brand Name": "Acer", "Series": "E5-575G", "Item model number": "E5-575G-76YK", "Operating System": "Windows 10", "Item Weight": "5.3 pounds", "Product Dimensions": "15 x 10.2 x 1.2 inches", "Item Dimensions  L x W x H": "15.02 x 10.2 x 1.19 inches", "Color": "Obsidian Black", "Processor Brand": "Intel", "Processor Count": "1", "Computer Memory Type": "DDR4 SDRAM", "Flash Memory Size": "256.0", "Power Source": "Battery", "Batteries": "1 Lithium ion batteries required. (included)", "ASIN": "B01F1Z78GM", "Customer Reviews": "", "Best Sellers Rank": "", "Shipping Weight": "7.1 pounds (", "Domestic Shipping": "Currently, item can be shipped only within the U.S. and to APO/FPO addresses. For APO/FPO shipments, please check with the manufacturer regarding warranty and support issues.", "International Shipping": "This item is not eligible for international shipping.", "Date First Available": "May 15, 2016", "Price": "$699.99", "Product Name": "Acer Aspire E 15 E5-575G-76YK 15.6-inch Full HD Notebook(Intel Core i7, NVIDIA 940MX,8 GB ,256GB SSD, Windows 10 Home 64-bit Edition),Black"},
{"Screen Size": "14 inches", "Max Screen Resolution": "1366 x 768 pixels", "Processor": "1.6 GHz Intel Celeron", "RAM": "4 GB DDR3 SDRAM", "Hard Drive": "32 GB emmc", "Card Description": "Integrated", "Wireless Type": "802.11 A/C", "Number of USB 3.0 Ports": "2", "Brand Name": "HP", "Series": "Stream", "Item model number": "14-ax010nr", "Operating System": "Windows 10", "Item Weight": "3.2 pounds", "Product Dimensions": "8.9 x 13.3 x 0.7 inches", "Item Dimensions  L x W x H": "8.9 x 13.27 x 0.7 inches", "Color": "Aqua Blue", "Processor Brand": "Intel", "Processor Count": "2", "Flash Memory Size": "32.0", "Batteries": "1 Lithium ion batteries required. (included)", "ASIN": "B01JLCKP34", "Customer Reviews": "", "Best Sellers Rank": "", "Shipping Weight": "4.7 pounds (", "Domestic Shipping": "Currently, item can be shipped only within the U.S. and to APO/FPO addresses. For APO/FPO shipments, please check with the manufacturer regarding warranty and support issues.", "International Shipping": "This item is not eligible for international shipping.", "Date First Available": "September 1, 2016", "Price": "$219.99", "Product Name": "HP Stream Laptop PC 14-ax010nr (Intel Celeron N3060, 4 GB RAM, 32 GB eMMC) with Office 365 Personal for one year"},
{"Screen Size": "15.4 inches", "Processor": "2.6 GHz Intel Core i7", "RAM": "16 GB LPDDR3", "Hard Drive": "256 GB", "Graphics Coprocessor": "integrated_graphics", "Chipset Brand": "intel", "Card Description": "integrated", "Brand Name": "Apple", "Series": "MLH32LL/A", "Item model number": "MLH32LL/A", "Operating System": "Mac OS Sierra", "Item Weight": "4 pounds", "Product Dimensions": "9.5 x 13.8 x 0.6 inches", "Item Dimensions  L x W x H": "9.48 x 13.75 x 0.61 inches", "Color": "Space Gray", "Processor Brand": "Intel", "Processor Count": "1", "Hard Drive Interface": "PCIE x 8", "Battery Type": "Lithium Polymer (LiPo)", "ASIN": "B01LTHXA72", "Customer Reviews": "", "Best Sellers Rank": "", "Shipping Weight": "6.7 pounds (", "Domestic Shipping": "Currently, item can be shipped only within the U.S. and to APO/FPO addresses. For APO/FPO shipments, please check with the manufacturer regarding warranty and support issues.", "International Shipping": "This item is not eligible for international shipping.", "Date First Available": "October 29, 2016", "Price": "$2,249.00", "Product Name": "Apple MacBook Pro MLH32LL/A 15.4-inch Laptop with Touch Bar (2.6GHz quad-core Intel Core i7, 256GB Retina Display), Space Gray"},
{"Screen Size": "15.6 inches", "Max Screen Resolution": "1920 x 1080 (1080P Full HD)", "Processor": "2.3 GHz Intel Core i5", "RAM": "8 GB DDR3 SDRAM", "Hard Drive": "1 TB HDD 5400 rpm", "Graphics Coprocessor": "integrated_graphics", "Chipset Brand": "intel", "Card Description": "integrated", "Wireless Type": "802.11A, 802.11bgn, Bluetooth", "Brand Name": "Dell", "Series": "Dell 5000 Series", "Item model number": "Dell Inspiron 15", "Hardware Platform": "PC", "Operating System": "Windows 10", "Item Weight": "5.4 pounds", "Product Dimensions": "15 x 10.2 x 0.9 inches", "Item Dimensions  L x W x H": "15 x 10.25 x 0.94 inches", "Color": "Silver", "Processor Brand": "Intel Core i5-6200U", "Processor Count": "2", "Computer Memory Type": "DDR3 SDRAM", "Hard Drive Interface": "Serial ATA", "Hard Drive Rotational Speed": "5400 RPM", "Power Source": "AC & Battery", "ASIN": "B01N0K3246", "Customer Reviews": "", "Best Sellers Rank": "", "Shipping Weight": "7.7 pounds (", "Date First Available": "November 28, 2016", "Price": "$445.00", "Product Name": "2017 Newest Dell Inspiron 15.6\" FHD Touchscreen Signature Laptop, Intel Core i5-6200U, 8 GB RAM, 1 TB HDD, DVD, Backlit keyboard, HDMI, Bluetooth, 802.11ac, RealSense 3D Webcam, Win10-MaxxAudio Pro"},
{"Screen Size": "15.6 inches", "Max Screen Resolution": "1920x1080 pixels", "Processor": "2.6 GHz Intel Core i7", "RAM": "16 GB", "Memory Speed": "2133 MHz", "Hard Drive": "1 TB mechanical_hard_drive", "Chipset Brand": "NVIDIA", "Card Description": "Dedicated", "Wireless Type": "802.11 A/C", "Number of USB 3.0 Ports": "3", "Average Battery Life (in hours)": "5 hours", "Brand Name": "Asus", "Series": "Republic Of Gamers", "Item model number": "GL502VM-DB71", "Operating System": "Windows 10", "Item Weight": "4.9 pounds", "Product Dimensions": "10.5 x 15.4 x 0.9 inches", "Item Dimensions  L x W x H": "10.5 x 15.4 x 0.9 inches", "Color": "black", "Processor Brand": "Intel", "Processor Count": "4", "Computer Memory Type": "GDDR5", "Hard Drive Rotational Speed": "7200 RPM", "Voltage": "19.5 volts", "Batteries": "1 Lithium ion batteries required. (included)", "ASIN": "B01KB0WJ1G", "Customer Reviews": "", "Best Sellers Rank": "", "Shipping Weight": "9.7 pounds (", "Domestic Shipping": "Currently, item can be shipped only within the U.S. and to APO/FPO addresses. For APO/FPO shipments, please check with the manufacturer regarding warranty and support issues.", "International Shipping": "This item is not eligible for international shipping.", "Date First Available": "August 17, 2016", "Price": "$1,299.00", "Product Name": "ASUS ROG STRIX 15.6-inch G-SYNC VR Ready Core i7 2.6GHz Thin and Light Gaming Laptop [GL502VM] GeForce GTX 1060, 16GB DDR4, 1TB 7200 RPM HDD, Intel Core i7 6700HQ"},
{"Screen Size": "15.6 inches", "Max Screen Resolution": "1366 x 768 (HD)", "Processor": "1.6 GHz Intel Pentium 4", "RAM": "4 GB DDR3 SDRAM", "Hard Drive": "500 GB HDD 5400 rpm", "Graphics Coprocessor": "integrated_graphics", "Chipset Brand": "intel", "Card Description": "integrated", "Wireless Type": "802.11bgn, Bluetooth", "Brand Name": "Asus", "Series": "Asus X Series", "Item model number": "Asus VivoBook", "Hardware Platform": "PC", "Operating System": "Windows 10", "Item Weight": "4.5 pounds", "Product Dimensions": "15 x 9.9 x 1 inches", "Item Dimensions  L x W x H": "15 x 9.92 x 1 inches", "Color": "Silver", "Processor Brand": "Pentium N3700", "Processor Count": "4", "Computer Memory Type": "DDR3 SDRAM", "Hard Drive Interface": "Serial ATA", "Hard Drive Rotational Speed": "5400 RPM", "Power Source": "AC & Battery", "ASIN": "B01MD0X9UP", "Customer Reviews": "", "Best Sellers Rank": "", "Shipping Weight": "5.8 pounds (", "Date First Available": "August 28, 2016", "Price": "$274.00", "Product Name": "2017 Newest ASUS 15.6\u201d High Performance Premium HD Laptop (Intel Quad Core Pentium N3700 Processor up to 2.4 GHz, 4GB RAM, 500GB HDD, SuperMulti DVD, Wifi, HDMI, VGA, Webcam, Windows 10-silver)"},
{"Screen Size": "11.6 inches", "Max Screen Resolution": "1366*768 pixels", "Processor": "1.8 GHz None", "RAM": "4 GB", "Hard Drive": "16 GB Flash Memory Solid State", "Card Description": "Dedicated", "Wireless Type": "802.11 A/C", "Number of USB 2.0 Ports": "2", "Average Battery Life (in hours)": "13 hours", "Brand Name": "Asus", "Series": "Chromebook", "Item model number": "C201PA-DS02-PW", "Operating System": "Chrome", "Item Weight": "2 pounds", "Product Dimensions": "11.3 x 7.6 x 0.7 inches", "Item Dimensions  L x W x H": "11.3 x 7.6 x 0.7 inches", "Color": "Pearl White/Light Blue", "Processor Brand": "Rockchip", "Processor Count": "1", "Flash Memory Size": "16.0", "Optical Drive Type": "None", "Batteries": "1 Lithium Polymer batteries required. (included)", "ASIN": "B01EGBAQXY", "Customer Reviews": "", "Best Sellers Rank": "", "Shipping Weight": "3.2 pounds (", "Domestic Shipping": "Currently, item can be shipped only within the U.S. and to APO/FPO addresses. For APO/FPO shipments, please check with the manufacturer regarding warranty and support issues.", "International Shipping": "This item can be shipped to select countries outside of the U.S.", "Date First Available": "June 5, 2016", "Price": "$199.00", "Product Name": "ASUS C201 11.6 Inch Chromebook (Rockchip, 4 GB, 16GB SSD, Pearl White/Light Blue)"},
{"Screen Size": "15.6 inches", "Max Screen Resolution": "1366 x 768 (HD)", "Processor": "1.6 GHz Intel Celeron", "RAM": "4 GB DDR3 SDRAM", "Hard Drive": "500 GB mechanical_hard_drive", "Graphics Coprocessor": "integrated_graphics", "Chipset Brand": "intel", "Card Description": "integrated", "Wireless Type": "802.11A, Bluetooth, 802.11bgn", "Average Battery Life (in hours)": "4 hours", "Brand Name": "Lenovo", "Series": "Lenovo ideapad 110", "Item model number": "Lenovo ideapad 15", "Hardware Platform": "PC", "Operating System": "Windows 10", "Item Weight": "4.8 pounds", "Product Dimensions": "15 x 10 x 0.9 inches", "Item Dimensions  L x W x H": "15 x 10 x 0.9 inches", "Processor Brand": "Intel N3060", "Processor Count": "2", "Computer Memory Type": "DDR3 SDRAM", "Hard Drive Interface": "Serial ATA", "Hard Drive Rotational Speed": "5400 RPM", "Power Source": "AC & Battery", "Batteries": "1 Lithium ion batteries required.", "ASIN": "B01MD0VMF2", "Customer Reviews": "", "Best Sellers Rank": "", "Shipping Weight": "5.9 pounds (", "Date First Available": "May 18, 2016", "Price": "$237.48", "Product Name": "Lenovo IdeaPad110 15.6-Inch HD Laptop (Intel Celeron N3060 Dual-Core Processor, 4GB RAM, 500GB HDD, Windows 10), Black"},
{"Screen Size": "11.6 inches", "Max Screen Resolution": "1366x768 pixels", "Processor": "2.16 GHz Intel Celeron", "RAM": "4 GB DDR3L SDRAM", "Memory Speed": "1600 MHz", "Hard Drive": "16 GB SSD", "Graphics Coprocessor": "integrated_graphics", "Chipset Brand": "Intel HD Graphics", "Card Description": "Integrated", "Wireless Type": "802.11 A/C", "Number of USB 3.0 Ports": "1", "Average Battery Life (in hours)": "11 hours", "Brand Name": "Samsung", "Series": "Chromebook 3", "Item model number": "XE500C13-K02US", "Hardware Platform": "PC", "Operating System": "Chrome", "Item Weight": "2.5 pounds", "Product Dimensions": "11.4 x 8 x 0.7 inches", "Item Dimensions  L x W x H": "11.37 x 8.04 x 0.7 inches", "Color": "Black", "Processor Brand": "Intel", "Processor Count": "1", "Flash Memory Size": "16.0", "Hard Drive Rotational Speed": "1 RPM", "Optical Drive Type": "None", "Batteries": "1 Lithium ion batteries required. (included)", "ASIN": "B01APA662K", "Customer Reviews": "", "Best Sellers Rank": "", "Shipping Weight": "3.9 pounds (", "Domestic Shipping": "Currently, item can be shipped only within the U.S. and to APO/FPO addresses. For APO/FPO shipments, please check with the manufacturer regarding warranty and support issues.", "International Shipping": "This item is not eligible for international shipping.", "Date First Available": "February 15, 2016", "Price": "$179.00", "Product Name": "Samsung Chromebook 3 XE500C13-K02US 4 GB RAM 16GB SSD 11.6\" Laptop (Black)"},
{"Screen Size": "15.6 inches", "Max Screen Resolution": "1366 x 768", "Processor": "2.4 GHz Intel Core 2 Duo", "RAM": "8 GB SDRAM DDR4", "Hard Drive": "1 TB HDD 5400 rpm", "Graphics Coprocessor": "integrated_graphics", "Chipset Brand": "intel", "Card Description": "integrated", "Wireless Type": "802.11 B/G, 802.11bgn, 802.11B", "Brand Name": "HP", "Series": "15-ay191ms", "Item model number": "15-ay191ms", "Hardware Platform": "PC", "Operating System": "Windows 10", "Item Weight": "4.6 pounds", "Product Dimensions": "15 x 10 x 0.9 inches", "Item Dimensions  L x W x H": "15 x 10 x 0.9 inches", "Processor Brand": "Intel", "Processor Count": "2", "Computer Memory Type": "DDR3 SDRAM", "Hard Drive Interface": "ATA", "ASIN": "B01MQOXCYY", "Customer Reviews": "", "Best Sellers Rank": "", "Shipping Weight": "6.5 pounds (", "Date First Available": "November 27, 2016", "Price": "$354.99", "Product Name": "2017 Newest HP Flagship 15.6\" 15-ay191ms HD Touchscreen Signature Edition Laptop (Intel Core i3-7100u 2.40 GHz, 8 GB DDR4 Memory, 1 TB HDD, DVD Burner, HDMI, HD Webcam, Bluetooth, Win 10)"},
{"Screen Size": "15.6 inches", "Max Screen Resolution": "3820*2160 pixels", "Processor": "2.6 GHz Intel Core i7", "RAM": "16 GB", "Hard Drive": "512 GB flash_memory_solid_state", "Graphics Coprocessor": "Nvidia GTX 960M 2G", "Chipset Brand": "nvidia", "Card Description": "dedicated", "Wireless Type": "802.11 A/C", "Number of USB 3.0 Ports": "3", "Brand Name": "Asus", "Series": "Zenbook", "Item model number": "UX501VW-US71T", "Operating System": "Windows 10", "Item Weight": "5 pounds", "Product Dimensions": "10 x 0.8 x 15.1 inches", "Item Dimensions  L x W x H": "10 x 0.8 x 15.1 inches", "Processor Brand": "Intel", "Processor Count": "4", "Computer Memory Type": "DDR4 SDRAM", "Flash Memory Size": "512", "Batteries": "1 Lithium ion batteries required. (included)", "ASIN": "B01CQRNBJG", "Customer Reviews": "", "Best Sellers Rank": "", "Shipping Weight": "8.4 pounds (", "Domestic Shipping": "Currently, item can be shipped only within the U.S. and to APO/FPO addresses. For APO/FPO shipments, please check with the manufacturer regarding warranty and support issues.", "International Shipping": "This item is not eligible for international shipping.", "Date First Available": "March 1, 2016", "Price": "$1,499.00", "Product Name": "ASUS ZenBook Pro UX501VW 15.6-Inch 4K Touchscreen Laptop (Core i7-6700HQ CPU, 16 GB DDR4, 512 GB NVMe SSD, GTX960M GPU, Thunderbolt III, Windows 10 Home)"},
{"Screen Size": "15.6 inches", "Screen Resolution": "1920 x 1080 pixels", "Max Screen Resolution": "1920*1080 pixels", "Processor": "2.6 GHz Intel Core i7", "RAM": "16 GB DDR4-SDRAM", "Memory Speed": "2133 MHz", "Hard Drive": "1 TB HDD", "Graphics Coprocessor": "NVIDIA GTX960M 2GB GDDR5", "Chipset Brand": "NVIDIA GeForce", "Card Description": "dedicated", "Graphics Card Ram Size": "2048 MB", "Wireless Type": "802.11 A/C", "Number of USB 2.0 Ports": "1", "Number of USB 3.0 Ports": "2", "Brand Name": "Asus", "Series": "ROG GL552VW", "Item model number": "GL552VW-DH71", "Hardware Platform": "PC", "Operating System": "Windows 10", "Item Weight": "5.6 pounds", "Product Dimensions": "10.1 x 15.1 x 1.3 inches", "Item Dimensions  L x W x H": "10.1 x 15.1 x 1.3 inches", "Color": "Metallic", "Processor Brand": "Intel", "Processor Count": "4", "Computer Memory Type": "GDDR3", "Hard Drive Interface": "Serial ATA-600", "Hard Drive Rotational Speed": "7200 RPM", "Optical Drive Type": "DL DVD\u00b1RW/CD-RW", "Voltage": "19 volts", "Batteries": "1 Lithium ion batteries required. (included)", "ASIN": "B01578ZKPO", "Customer Reviews": "", "Best Sellers Rank": "", "Shipping Weight": "9.5 pounds (", "Domestic Shipping": "Currently, item can be shipped only within the U.S. and to APO/FPO addresses. For APO/FPO shipments, please check with the manufacturer regarding warranty and support issues.", "International Shipping": "This item is not eligible for international shipping.", "Date First Available": "October 9, 2015", "Price": "$1,027.16", "Product Name": "ASUS ROG GL552VW-DH71 15-Inch Gaming Laptop, Discrete GPU GeForce GTX 960M 2GB VRAM, 16GB DDR4, 1TB (ROG Metallic)"},
{"Screen Size": "13.3 inches", "Max Screen Resolution": "1366x768 pixels", "Processor": "1.6 GHz None", "RAM": "4 GB DDR3 SDRAM", "Hard Drive": "Flash Memory Solid State", "Card Description": "Integrated", "Number of USB 3.0 Ports": "2", "Average Battery Life (in hours)": "10 hours", "Brand Name": "Asus", "Item model number": "C300SA-DH02", "Operating System": "Chrome", "Item Weight": "3.1 pounds", "Product Dimensions": "9.1 x 13 x 0.8 inches", "Item Dimensions  L x W x H": "9.1 x 13 x 0.8 inches", "Color": "Black", "Processor Brand": "Intel", "Processor Count": "2", "Flash Memory Size": "16.0", "Optical Drive Type": "None", "Batteries": "1 Lithium ion batteries required. (included)", "ASIN": "B01MG696PV", "Customer Reviews": "", "Best Sellers Rank": "", "Shipping Weight": "4.7 pounds (", "Domestic Shipping": "Currently, item can be shipped only within the U.S. and to APO/FPO addresses. For APO/FPO shipments, please check with the manufacturer regarding warranty and support issues.", "International Shipping": "This item is not eligible for international shipping.", "Date First Available": "October 18, 2016", "Price": "$209.00", "Product Name": "ASUS 13.3-inch Black Chromebook [C300AS] Intel Celeron N3060 1.6GHz Processor, 4GB 1866MHz DDR3 Memory, 16GB Flash Storage, HDMI, USB 3.0, SD Card, 15-hour Battery-Life, 802.11AC WiFi"},
{"Screen Size": "13.3 inches", "Screen Resolution": "3200 x 1200", "Max Screen Resolution": "3200*1800 pixels", "Processor": "2.5 GHz Intel Core i7", "RAM": "12 GB DDR3", "Memory Speed": "1600 MHz", "Hard Drive": "512 GB SSD", "Graphics Coprocessor": "Nvidia GT940M 2GB", "Chipset Brand": "nvidia", "Card Description": "dedicated", "Wireless Type": "802.11 A/C", "Number of USB 3.0 Ports": "3", "Brand Name": "Asus", "Series": "ZenBook", "Item model number": "UX303UB-DH74T", "Hardware Platform": "PC", "Operating System": "Windows 10", "Item Weight": "3.2 pounds", "Product Dimensions": "8.8 x 12.7 x 0.8 inches", "Item Dimensions  L x W x H": "8.8 x 12.7 x 0.8 inches", "Color": "Smokey Brown", "Processor Brand": "Intel", "Processor Count": "2", "Computer Memory Type": "DDR3 SDRAM", "Flash Memory Size": "512", "Hard Drive Interface": "Solid State", "Optical Drive Type": "None", "Power Source": "Battery", "Batteries": "1 Lithium ion batteries required. (included)", "ASIN": "B014VHVZFQ", "Customer Reviews": "", "Best Sellers Rank": "", "Shipping Weight": "6.5 pounds (", "Domestic Shipping": "Currently, item can be shipped only within the U.S. and to APO/FPO addresses. For APO/FPO shipments, please check with the manufacturer regarding warranty and support issues.", "International Shipping": "This item is not eligible for international shipping.", "Date First Available": "September 25, 2015", "Price": "$1,202.99", "Product Name": "ASUS ZenBook UX303UB 13.3-Inch QHD+ Touchscreen Laptop, Intel Core i7, 12 GB RAM, 512 GB SSD, Discrete GPU Nvidia GT940M, Windows 10 (64 bit)"},
{"Screen Size": "13.3 inches", "Screen Resolution": "1920 x 1080 pixels", "Max Screen Resolution": "1920*1080 pixels", "Processor": "2.3 GHz Intel Core i5", "RAM": "8 GB DDR3", "Memory Speed": "1600 MHz", "Hard Drive": "256 GB SSD", "Graphics Coprocessor": "Intel HD", "Card Description": "integrated", "Wireless Type": "802.11 A/C", "Number of USB 3.0 Ports": "3", "Average Battery Life (in hours)": "7 hours", "Brand Name": "Asus", "Series": "ZenBook", "Item model number": "UX303UA-DH51T", "Hardware Platform": "PC", "Operating System": "Windows 10", "Item Weight": "3.2 pounds", "Product Dimensions": "8.8 x 12.7 x 0.8 inches", "Item Dimensions  L x W x H": "8.8 x 12.7 x 0.8 inches", "Color": "Smokey Brown", "Processor Brand": "Intel", "Processor Count": "2", "Computer Memory Type": "DDR3 SDRAM", "Flash Memory Size": "256", "Hard Drive Interface": "Solid State", "Optical Drive Type": "No", "Audio-out Ports (#)": "1", "Battery Type": "Lithium Polymer (LiPo)", "Power Source": "AC", "Batteries": "1 Lithium ion batteries required. (included)", "ASIN": "B014VHW24Y", "Customer Reviews": "", "Best Sellers Rank": "", "Shipping Weight": "6.6 pounds (", "Domestic Shipping": "Currently, item can be shipped only within the U.S. and to APO/FPO addresses. For APO/FPO shipments, please check with the manufacturer regarding warranty and support issues.", "International Shipping": "This item is not eligible for international shipping.", "Date First Available": "September 25, 2015", "Price": "$829.00", "Product Name": "ASUS ZenBook UX303UA 13.3-Inch FHD Touchscreen Laptop, Intel Core i5, 8 GB RAM, 256 GB SSD, Windows 10 (64 bit)"},
{"Screen Size": "13.3 inches", "Screen Resolution": "1440x900", "Max Screen Resolution": "1440 x 900", "Processor": "2.7 GHz Intel Core i5", "RAM": "8 GB SODIMM", "Memory Speed": "1600 MHz", "Hard Drive": "256 GB", "Graphics Coprocessor": "integrated_graphics", "Chipset Brand": "intel", "Wireless Type": "802.11B, 802.11G, 802.11n", "Average Battery Life (in hours)": "12 hours", "Brand Name": "Apple", "Series": "Macbook Air", "Item model number": "MMGG2LL/A", "Hardware Platform": "Mac", "Operating System": "Mac OS X", "Item Weight": "3 pounds", "Product Dimensions": "12.8 x 8.9 x 0.7 inches", "Item Dimensions  L x W x H": "12.8 x 8.94 x 0.68 inches", "Processor Brand": "Intel", "Processor Count": "2", "Computer Memory Type": "SODIMM", "Flash Memory Size": "256", "Hard Drive Interface": "Solid State", "Batteries": "1 Lithium ion batteries required.", "ASIN": "B01I19M3KG", "Customer Reviews": "", "Best Sellers Rank": "", "Shipping Weight": "6.4 pounds (", "Date First Available": "July 6, 2016", "Price": "$1,109.89", "Product Name": "Apple MacBook Air MMGG2LL/A 13.3-Inch Laptop (Intel Core i5, 8GB RAM, 256GB, Mac OS X), 2016 Version"},
{"Screen Size": "13.3 inches", "Screen Resolution": "1920 x 1080 pixels", "Max Screen Resolution": "1920*1080 pixels", "Processor": "0.9 GHz Core M 6Y30", "RAM": "8 GB LPDDR3-SDRAM", "Memory Speed": "1866 MHz", "Hard Drive": "512 GB 512 GB Solid State Drive", "Graphics Coprocessor": "integrated_graphics", "Chipset Brand": "intel", "Card Description": "Integrated", "Wireless Type": "802.11 A/C", "Number of USB 3.0 Ports": "2", "Brand Name": "Asus", "Series": "ZENBOOK", "Item model number": "UX360CA-DBM2T", "Hardware Platform": "PC", "Operating System": "Windows 10", "Item Weight": "2.9 pounds", "Product Dimensions": "17.6 x 10.4 x 2.2 inches", "Item Dimensions  L x W x H": "17.6 x 10.4 x 2.2 inches", "Color": "Gray (aluminum)", "Processor Brand": "Intel", "Processor Count": "2", "Computer Memory Type": "DDR3 SDRAM", "Flash Memory Size": "512", "Hard Drive Interface": "Solid State", "Optical Drive Type": "No", "Battery Type": "Polymer", "Voltage": "19 volts", "Batteries": "1 Lithium Polymer batteries required. (included)", "ASIN": "B01GHQOD8U", "Customer Reviews": "", "Best Sellers Rank": "", "Shipping Weight": "6 pounds (", "Domestic Shipping": "Currently, item can be shipped only within the U.S. and to APO/FPO addresses. For APO/FPO shipments, please check with the manufacturer regarding warranty and support issues.", "International Shipping": "This item can be shipped to select countries outside of the U.S.", "Date First Available": "June 2, 2016", "Price": "$705.49", "Product Name": "ASUS ZenBook Flip UX360CA-DBM2T 13.3 - inch Touchscreen Laptop (Intel Core M CPU,8 GB RAM,512 GB Solid State Drive,Windows 10)"},
{"Screen Size": "13.3 inches", "Max Screen Resolution": "1920 x 1080 pixels", "Processor": "0.9 GHz None", "RAM": "8 GB DDR3 SDRAM", "Hard Drive": "256 GB Flash Memory Solid State", "Card Description": "Integrated", "Wireless Type": "802.11 A/C", "Number of USB 3.0 Ports": "2", "Brand Name": "Asus", "Series": "UX360", "Item model number": "UX360CA-UBM1T", "Hardware Platform": "PC", "Operating System": "Windows 10", "Item Weight": "2.9 pounds", "Product Dimensions": "8.7 x 12.7 x 0.5 inches", "Item Dimensions  L x W x H": "8.7 x 12.7 x 0.5 inches", "Processor Brand": "Intel", "Processor Count": "2", "Computer Memory Type": "SODIMM", "Flash Memory Size": "256.0", "Hard Drive Interface": "SSA", "Optical Drive Type": "None", "Batteries": "1 Lithium ion batteries required. (included)", "ASIN": "B01HZT6AR0", "Customer Reviews": "", "Best Sellers Rank": "", "Shipping Weight": "6.7 pounds (", "Domestic Shipping": "Currently, item can be shipped only within the U.S. and to APO/FPO addresses. For APO/FPO shipments, please check with the manufacturer regarding warranty and support issues.", "International Shipping": "This item is not eligible for international shipping.", "Date First Available": "July 5, 2016", "Price": "$554.96", "Product Name": "ASUS ZenBook Flip UX360CA-UBM1T 13.3-inch Touchscreen Convertible Laptop Core m3 8GB DDR3 256GB SSD with Windows 10"},
{"Screen Size": "15.6 inches", "Max Screen Resolution": "1920 x 1080 (1080P Full HD)", "Processor": "2.3 GHz Intel Core i5", "RAM": "8 GB SDRAM DDR3", "Hard Drive": "1 TB HDD 5400 rpm", "Graphics Coprocessor": "Intel Integrated Graphics", "Chipset Brand": "intel", "Card Description": "integrated", "Wireless Type": "802.11abg, 802.11n, Bluetooth", "Brand Name": "delli58gb", "Series": "DELL 5000", "Item model number": "DELL 5000", "Hardware Platform": "PC", "Operating System": "Windows 10", "Item Weight": "5.4 pounds", "Product Dimensions": "15 x 1 x 10 inches", "Item Dimensions  L x W x H": "15 x 1 x 10 inches", "Color": "Silver Matte", "Processor Brand": "Intel", "Processor Count": "2", "Computer Memory Type": "DDR3 SDRAM", "Hard Drive Interface": "Serial ATA", "Hard Drive Rotational Speed": "5400 RPM", "Power Source": "AC & Battery", "ASIN": "B01M161UFE", "Customer Reviews": "", "Best Sellers Rank": "", "Shipping Weight": "7.4 pounds (", "Date First Available": "April 7, 2016", "Price": "$418.00", "Product Name": "2016 Newest Dell Inspiron 15 5000 15.6\" FHD Touchscreen Laptop, Intel Core i5-6200U, 8 GB RAM, 1 TB HDD, DVD, Backlit keyboard, HDMI, Bluetooth, 802.11ac, RealSense 3D Webcam, Windows 10-MaxxAudio Pro"},
{"Screen Size": "14 inches", "Max Screen Resolution": "1920x1080 pixels", "Processor": "2.6 GHz Intel Core i7", "RAM": "16 GB", "Memory Speed": "2133 MHz", "Hard Drive": "512 GB flash_memory_solid_state", "Chipset Brand": "nvidia", "Card Description": "Dedicated", "Wireless Type": "802.11abg", "Number of USB 3.0 Ports": "3", "Brand Name": "Razer", "Series": "Blade", "Item model number": "RZ09-01952E72-R3U1", "Operating System": "Windows 10", "Item Weight": "4.2 pounds", "Product Dimensions": "13.6 x 9.3 x 0.7 inches", "Item Dimensions  L x W x H": "13.6 x 9.3 x 0.7 inches", "Processor Brand": "Intel", "Processor Count": "4", "Computer Memory Type": "GDDR5", "Flash Memory Size": "512", "Batteries": "1 Lithium ion batteries required. (included)", "ASIN": "B01LZTCMPA", "Customer Reviews": "", "Best Sellers Rank": "", "Shipping Weight": "8.4 pounds (", "Domestic Shipping": "Currently, item can be shipped only within the U.S. and to APO/FPO addresses. For APO/FPO shipments, please check with the manufacturer regarding warranty and support issues.", "International Shipping": "This item can be shipped to select countries outside of the U.S.", "Date First Available": "September 11, 2016", "Price": "$1,999.99", "Product Name": "The Razer Blade (GeForce GTX 1060) 14\" HD Gaming Laptop (6th Gen Intel Core i7, 16GB RAM, 512GB SSD) - VR Ready"},
{"Screen Size": "14 inches", "Max Screen Resolution": "1920 x 1080 pixels", "Processor": "1.6 GHz None", "RAM": "4 GB DDR3 SDRAM", "Hard Drive": "emmc", "Card Description": "Integrated", "Wireless Type": "802.11 A/C", "Number of USB 3.0 Ports": "1", "Brand Name": "Asus", "Series": "Eeebook", "Item model number": "R416SA-EH21", "Operating System": "Windows 10", "Item Weight": "3.3 pounds", "Product Dimensions": "9.3 x 13.3 x 0.7 inches", "Item Dimensions  L x W x H": "9.3 x 13.3 x 0.7 inches", "Processor Brand": "Intel", "Processor Count": "4", "Batteries": "1 Lithium ion batteries required. (included)", "ASIN": "B01LWY7U8G", "Customer Reviews": "", "Best Sellers Rank": "", "Shipping Weight": "4.8 pounds (", "Domestic Shipping": "Currently, item can be shipped only within the U.S. and to APO/FPO addresses. For APO/FPO shipments, please check with the manufacturer regarding warranty and support issues.", "International Shipping": "This item is not eligible for international shipping.", "Date First Available": "September 21, 2016", "Price": "$399.00", "Product Name": "ASUS VivoBook R416SA-EH21 14\" Full HD Laptop (Quad-Core N3700, 4GB DDR3 RAM, 128GB eMMC, Windows 10), Metallic Gray"},
{"Screen Size": "11.6 inches", "Max Screen Resolution": "1366 x 768 pixels", "Processor": "1.44 GHz None", "RAM": "4 GB DDR3 SDRAM", "Memory Speed": "1600 MHz", "Hard Drive": "32 GB emmc", "Card Description": "Integrated", "Wireless Type": "802.11 A/C", "Number of USB 2.0 Ports": "1", "Number of USB 3.0 Ports": "1", "Brand Name": "Asus", "Series": "VivoBook", "Item model number": "E200HA-UB02-GD", "Operating System": "Windows 10", "Item Weight": "2.2 pounds", "Product Dimensions": "7.6 x 11.3 x 0.7 inches", "Item Dimensions  L x W x H": "7.6 x 11.3 x 0.7 inches", "Processor Brand": "Intel", "Processor Count": "4", "Computer Memory Type": "DDR3 SDRAM", "Flash Memory Size": "32", "Voltage": "19 volts", "Batteries": "1 Lithium ion batteries required. (included)", "ASIN": "B01LT692RK", "Customer Reviews": "", "Best Sellers Rank": "", "Shipping Weight": "3.4 pounds (", "Domestic Shipping": "Currently, item can be shipped only within the U.S. and to APO/FPO addresses. For APO/FPO shipments, please check with the manufacturer regarding warranty and support issues.", "International Shipping": "This item is not eligible for international shipping.", "Date First Available": "September 8, 2016", "Price": "$199.00", "Product Name": "ASUS E200HA-UB02-GD Portable 11.6-Inch Intel Quad-Core Laptop 4GB RAM 32GB Storage, Windows 10, Aurora Gold."},
{"Screen Size": "15.6 inches", "Max Screen Resolution": "1366x768", "Processor": "3.3 GHz AMD A Series", "RAM": "8 GB SDRAM DDR3", "Hard Drive": "1 TB mechanical_hard_drive", "Chipset Brand": "amd", "Wireless Type": "802.11 B/G, 802.11bgn, 802.11B", "Average Battery Life (in hours)": "5 hours", "Brand Name": "Lenovo", "Series": "Lenovo Z50", "Item model number": "B01LW0F62Q", "Hardware Platform": "PC", "Operating System": "windows 10", "Item Weight": "5.6 pounds", "Product Dimensions": "15 x 11 x 1 inches", "Item Dimensions  L x W x H": "15 x 11 x 1 inches", "Color": "Black", "Processor Brand": "AMD", "Processor Count": "4", "Computer Memory Type": "DDR3 SDRAM", "Hard Drive Interface": "Serial ATA", "Hard Drive Rotational Speed": "5400 RPM", "ASIN": "B01LW0F62Q", "Customer Reviews": "", "Best Sellers Rank": "", "Shipping Weight": "6.8 pounds (", "Date First Available": "September 9, 2016", "Price": "$386.96", "Product Name": "2016 Newest Lenovo Premium Built High Performance 15.6 inch HD Laptop (AMD FX7500 Processor, 8GB RAM 1T HDD, DVD RW, Bluetooth, Webcam, WiFi, HDMI, Windows 10 ) - Black"},
{"Screen Size": "15.6 inches", "Screen Resolution": "1366 x 768 (HD)", "Max Screen Resolution": "1366 x 768 (HD)", "Processor": "2 MHz Core i3-550", "RAM": "6 GB SDRAM DDR3", "Memory Speed": "1600 MHz", "Hard Drive": "1 TB HDD 5400 rpm", "Chipset Brand": "intel", "Card Description": "integrated", "Wireless Type": "802.11A", "Number of USB 2.0 Ports": "2", "Brand Name": "Dell", "Series": "7000-2016-Gaming", "Item model number": "I3558-0954BLK", "Hardware Platform": "PC", "Operating System": "Windows 10", "Item Weight": "5 pounds", "Product Dimensions": "15.1 x 10.4 x 1 inches", "Item Dimensions  L x W x H": "15.1 x 10.4 x 1 inches", "Processor Brand": "Intel", "Processor Count": "2", "Computer Memory Type": "DDR3 SDRAM", "Hard Drive Interface": "Serial ATA", "Power Source": "AC & Battery", "ASIN": "B01LZ2ABKN", "Customer Reviews": "", "Best Sellers Rank": "", "Shipping Weight": "9.2 pounds (", "Date First Available": "October 5, 2016", "Price": "$317.94", "Product Name": "Dell Inspiron I3558-0954BLK Laptop 15.6-Inch Laptop (Intel Core i3-5005U 2 GHz ,6GB, 1TB Hard Drive Intel HD Graphics 5500, Windows 10 Home 64-bit), Black"},
{"Screen Size": "15.6 inches", "Max Screen Resolution": "1920*1080 pixels", "Processor": "2.1 GHz Intel Core i3", "RAM": "4 GB DDR3", "Memory Speed": "1600 MHz", "Hard Drive": "500 GB mechanical_hard_drive", "Graphics Coprocessor": "Intel HD", "Card Description": "integrated", "Wireless Type": "802.11 A/C", "Number of USB 2.0 Ports": "1", "Number of USB 3.0 Ports": "2", "Brand Name": "Asus", "Series": "F555LA", "Item model number": "F555LA-AB31", "Operating System": "Windows 10", "Item Weight": "5.1 pounds", "Product Dimensions": "10.1 x 15 x 1 inches", "Item Dimensions  L x W x H": "10.1 x 15 x 1 inches", "Color": "Black", "Processor Brand": "Intel", "Processor Count": "1", "Computer Memory Type": "DDR3 SDRAM", "Hard Drive Rotational Speed": "5400 RPM", "Optical Drive Type": "DL DVD\u00b1RW/CD-RW", "Batteries": "1 Lithium ion batteries required. (included)", "ASIN": "B011KFQASE", "Customer Reviews": "", "Best Sellers Rank": "", "Shipping Weight": "6.5 pounds (", "Domestic Shipping": "Currently, item can be shipped only within the U.S. and to APO/FPO addresses. For APO/FPO shipments, please check with the manufacturer regarding warranty and support issues.", "International Shipping": "This item is not eligible for international shipping.", "Date First Available": "August 1, 2015", "Price": "$437.99", "Product Name": "Asus F555LA-AB31 15.6-Inch Laptop (2.1 GHz Core i3-5010U Processor,4 GB RAM,500 GB Hard Drive, Windows 10), Black"},
{"Screen Size": "11.6 inches", "Max Screen Resolution": "1366*768 pixels", "Processor": "1.8 GHz None", "RAM": "4 GB DDR3 SDRAM", "Hard Drive": "16 GB flash_memory_solid_state", "Graphics Coprocessor": "integrated_graphics", "Chipset Brand": "intel", "Card Description": "Dedicated", "Wireless Type": "802.11 A/C", "Average Battery Life (in hours)": "13 hours", "Brand Name": "Asus", "Series": "Chromebook", "Item model number": "C201PA-DS02-LG", "Operating System": "Chrome", "Item Weight": "2 pounds", "Product Dimensions": "11.3 x 7.6 x 0.7 inches", "Item Dimensions  L x W x H": "11.3 x 7.6 x 0.7 inches", "Color": "Lotus Gold/Red", "Processor Brand": "Rockchip", "Processor Count": "1", "Flash Memory Size": "16.0", "Batteries": "1 Lithium ion batteries required. (included)", "ASIN": "B01EGBAR4W", "Customer Reviews": "", "Best Sellers Rank": "", "Shipping Weight": "2.6 pounds (", "Domestic Shipping": "Currently, item can be shipped only within the U.S. and to APO/FPO addresses. For APO/FPO shipments, please check with the manufacturer regarding warranty and support issues.", "International Shipping": "This item is not eligible for international shipping.", "Date First Available": "June 5, 2016", "Price": "$199.00", "Product Name": "ASUS C201PA-DS02-LG 11.6-Inch Chromebook (Rockchip RK3288 1.8GHz Quad-Core, 4GB DDR3, 16GB SSD + TPM, Chrome OS), Lotus Gold/Red"},
{"Screen Size": "15.4 inches", "Screen Resolution": "2880-by-1800", "Max Screen Resolution": "2880-by-1800", "Processor": "2.7 GHz Intel Core i7", "RAM": "16 GB LPDDR3", "Hard Drive": "512 GB", "Graphics Coprocessor": "Intel HD Graphics 530", "Chipset Brand": "intel", "Card Description": "integrated", "Brand Name": "Apple", "Series": "MLH42LL/A", "Item model number": "MLH42LL/A", "Hardware Platform": "Mac", "Operating System": "Mac OS Sierra", "Item Weight": "4 pounds", "Product Dimensions": "9.5 x 13.8 x 0.6 inches", "Item Dimensions  L x W x H": "9.48 x 13.75 x 0.61 inches", "Color": "Space Gray", "Processor Brand": "Intel", "Processor Count": "1", "Battery Type": "Lithium Polymer (LiPo)", "ASIN": "B01LTHXA7C", "Customer Reviews": "", "Best Sellers Rank": "", "Shipping Weight": "6.7 pounds (", "Domestic Shipping": "Currently, item can be shipped only within the U.S. and to APO/FPO addresses. For APO/FPO shipments, please check with the manufacturer regarding warranty and support issues.", "International Shipping": "This item is not eligible for international shipping.", "Date First Available": "October 29, 2016", "Price": "$2,649.99", "Product Name": "Apple MacBook Pro MLH42LL/A 15.4-inch Laptop with Touch Bar (2.7GHz quad-core Intel Core i7, 512GB Retina Display), Space Gray"},
{"Screen Size": "13.3 inches", "Max Screen Resolution": "1920x1080 pixels", "Processor": "2.5 GHz None", "RAM": "8 GB DDR3 SDRAM", "Hard Drive": "Flash Memory Solid State", "Graphics Coprocessor": "integrated_graphics", "Chipset Brand": "intel", "Card Description": "Integrated", "Number of USB 3.0 Ports": "3", "Brand Name": "HP", "Item model number": "13-ab016nr", "Operating System": "Windows 10", "Item Weight": "3.3 pounds", "Product Dimensions": "8.9 x 12.8 x 0.6 inches", "Item Dimensions  L x W x H": "8.9 x 12.83 x 0.55 inches", "Processor Brand": "Intel", "Processor Count": "2", "Flash Memory Size": "256.0", "Optical Drive Type": "DVD+R", "Batteries": "1 Lithium ion batteries required. (included)", "ASIN": "B01LZKY7RB", "Customer Reviews": "", "Best Sellers Rank": "", "Shipping Weight": "5.3 pounds (", "Domestic Shipping": "Currently, item can be shipped only within the U.S. and to APO/FPO addresses. For APO/FPO shipments, please check with the manufacturer regarding warranty and support issues.", "International Shipping": "This item is not eligible for international shipping.", "Date First Available": "October 23, 2016", "Price": "$699.99", "Product Name": "HP ENVY 13-ab016nr Notebook (Intel Core i5-7200U, 8GB RAM, 256GB SSD) with Windows 10"},
{"Screen Size": "14 inches", "Max Screen Resolution": "1366 x 768 pixels", "Processor": "1.6 GHz Intel Celeron", "RAM": "4 GB DDR3 SDRAM", "Hard Drive": "32 GB emmc", "Card Description": "Integrated", "Wireless Type": "802.11 A/C", "Number of USB 3.0 Ports": "2", "Brand Name": "HP", "Series": "Stream", "Item model number": "14-ax020nr", "Operating System": "Windows 10", "Item Weight": "3.2 pounds", "Product Dimensions": "8.9 x 13.3 x 0.7 inches", "Item Dimensions  L x W x H": "8.9 x 13.27 x 0.7 inches", "Color": "Violet/Purple", "Processor Brand": "Intel", "Processor Count": "2", "Flash Memory Size": "32.0", "Batteries": "1 Lithium ion batteries required. (included)", "ASIN": "B01JLCKP1Q", "Customer Reviews": "", "Best Sellers Rank": "", "Shipping Weight": "4.4 pounds (", "Domestic Shipping": "Currently, item can be shipped only within the U.S. and to APO/FPO addresses. For APO/FPO shipments, please check with the manufacturer regarding warranty and support issues.", "International Shipping": "This item is not eligible for international shipping.", "Date First Available": "September 1, 2016", "Product Name": "HP Stream Laptop PC 14-ax020nr (Intel Celeron N3060, 4 GB RAM, 32 GB eMMC) with Office 365 Personal for one year"},
{"Screen Size": "15.6 inches", "Screen Resolution": "1920 x 1080 pixels", "Max Screen Resolution": "1920X1080 pixels", "Processor": "2.6 GHz Core i7 6700HQ", "RAM": "12 GB SO-DIMM", "Memory Speed": "2133 MHz", "Hard Drive": "1000 GB SATA", "Graphics Coprocessor": "gddr5", "Chipset Brand": "GTX 970", "Card Description": "integrated", "Graphics Card Ram Size": "3000 MB", "Wireless Type": "802.11 A/C", "Number of USB 2.0 Ports": "1", "Number of USB 3.0 Ports": "2", "Brand Name": "MSI", "Series": "GE62", "Item model number": "GE62 Apache Pro-239", "Hardware Platform": "PC", "Operating System": "Windows 10", "Item Weight": "5.3 pounds", "Product Dimensions": "15.1 x 10.2 x 1.1 inches", "Item Dimensions  L x W x H": "15.07 x 10.23 x 1.06 inches", "Color": "Aluminum Black", "Processor Brand": "Intel", "Processor Count": "4", "Computer Memory Type": "GDDR5", "Hard Drive Interface": "Serial ATA", "Hard Drive Rotational Speed": "7200 RPM", "Optical Drive Type": "DVD+RW", "Audio-out Ports (#)": "1", "Battery Type": "Lithium-Ion (Li-Ion)", "Batteries": "1 Lithium ion batteries required. (included)", "ASIN": "B01D8VJ0B2", "Customer Reviews": "", "Best Sellers Rank": "", "Shipping Weight": "10.3 pounds (", "Domestic Shipping": "Currently, item can be shipped only within the U.S. and to APO/FPO addresses. For APO/FPO shipments, please check with the manufacturer regarding warranty and support issues.", "International Shipping": "This item can be shipped to select countries outside of the U.S.", "Date First Available": "April 1, 2016", "Price": "$999.99", "Product Name": "MSI GE62 Apache Pro-239 15.6\" GAMING LAPTOP NOTEBOOK GTX 970M i7-6700HQ 12GB 1TB WINDOWS 10 USB TYPE-C FULL COLOR KEYBOARD"},
{"Screen Size": "13.3 inches", "Screen Resolution": "2560-by-1600", "Max Screen Resolution": "2560-by-1600", "Processor": "2 GHz Intel Core i5", "RAM": "8 GB LPDDR3", "Memory Speed": "1866 MHz", "Hard Drive": "256 GB flash_memory_solid_state", "Graphics Coprocessor": "Intel HD Graphics 540", "Chipset Brand": "intel", "Wireless Type": "802.11B, 802.11G, 802.11n", "Brand Name": "Apple", "Series": "MLUQ2LL/A", "Item model number": "MLUQ2LL/A", "Hardware Platform": "Mac", "Operating System": "Mac OS Sierra", "Item Weight": "3 pounds", "Product Dimensions": "8.4 x 12 x 0.6 inches", "Item Dimensions  L x W x H": "8.36 x 11.97 x 0.59 inches", "Color": "Silver", "Processor Brand": "Intel", "Processor Count": "1", "Computer Memory Type": "DDR3 SDRAM", "Flash Memory Size": "256", "Optical Drive Type": "No", "Audio-out Ports (#)": "1", "Battery Type": "Lithium Polymer (LiPo)", "ASIN": "B01LTHXA9A", "Customer Reviews": "", "Best Sellers Rank": "", "Shipping Weight": "5.8 pounds (", "Domestic Shipping": "Currently, item can be shipped only within the U.S. and to APO/FPO addresses. For APO/FPO shipments, please check with the manufacturer regarding warranty and support issues.", "International Shipping": "This item is not eligible for international shipping.", "Date First Available": "October 29, 2016", "Price": "$1,379.00", "Product Name": "Apple MacBook Pro MLUQ2LL/A 13.3-inch Laptop (2.0GHz dual-core Intel Core i5, 256GB Retina Display), Silver"},
{"Screen Size": "14 inches", "Max Screen Resolution": "1366x768", "Processor": "2.1 GHz Pentium", "RAM": "4 GB SDRAM DDR4", "Memory Speed": "2133 MHz", "Hard Drive": "500 GB HDD 5400 rpm", "Graphics Coprocessor": "integrated_graphics", "Chipset Brand": "intel", "Card Description": "integrated", "Wireless Type": "802.11bgn, 802.11A", "Number of USB 2.0 Ports": "1", "Average Battery Life (in hours)": "8.5 hours", "Brand Name": "Lenovo", "Series": "flex 4 2 in 1", "Item model number": "flex 4 2 in 1", "Hardware Platform": "PC", "Operating System": "Windows 10", "Item Weight": "3.9 pounds", "Product Dimensions": "13.3 x 9.2 x 0.8 inches", "Item Dimensions  L x W x H": "13.3 x 9.2 x 0.8 inches", "Color": "Black", "Processor Brand": "Intel", "Processor Count": "2", "Computer Memory Type": "DDR3 SDRAM", "Hard Drive Interface": "Serial ATA", "Hard Drive Rotational Speed": "5400 RPM", "Power Source": "AC & Battery", "ASIN": "B01HAQBONI", "Customer Reviews": "", "Best Sellers Rank": "", "Shipping Weight": "5.5 pounds (", "Date First Available": "June 20, 2016", "Product Name": "Lenovo Flex 4 14 Inch Touchscreen Laptop Intel Pentium Dual-Core Processor, 4GB DDR4 RAM, 500GB HDD, Widnows 10, Black"},
{"Screen Size": "11.6 inches", "Screen Resolution": "1366x768", "Max Screen Resolution": "1366 x 768", "Processor": "1.6 GHz Intel Celeron", "RAM": "4 GB SDRAM DDR3", "Memory Speed": "1600 MHz", "Hard Drive": "64 GB SSD", "Graphics Coprocessor": "integrated_graphics", "Chipset Brand": "intel", "Card Description": "integrated", "Wireless Type": "802.11bgn, Bluetooth", "Number of USB 2.0 Ports": "2", "Average Battery Life (in hours)": "6.5 hours", "Brand Name": "Lenovo", "Series": "lenovo N22", "Item model number": "lenovo N22", "Hardware Platform": "PC", "Operating System": "Windows 10", "Item Weight": "2.8 pounds", "Product Dimensions": "11.8 x 8.5 x 0.9 inches", "Item Dimensions  L x W x H": "11.8 x 8.5 x 0.88 inches", "Color": "Black", "Processor Brand": "Intel", "Processor Count": "2", "Computer Memory Type": "DDR3 SDRAM", "Hard Drive Interface": "Serial ATA", "Audio-out Ports (#)": "1", "Power Source": "AC", "ASIN": "B01K9HS4Q0", "Customer Reviews": "", "Best Sellers Rank": "", "Shipping Weight": "4 pounds (", "Date First Available": "August 12, 2016", "Price": "$204.99", "Product Name": "Lenovo N22 11.6-inch High Performance Laptop Notebook (2016 New Premium Edition), Intel Dual-Core Processor 2.16GHz, 4GB RAM, 64GB SSD, Rotatable Webcam, Water-Resistant Keyboard, Windows 10 Pro"},
{"Screen Size": "15.6 inches", "Max Screen Resolution": "1920x1080 pixels", "Processor": "2.5 GHz Intel Core i7", "RAM": "8 GB DDR3 SDRAM", "Hard Drive": "256 GB flash_memory_solid_state", "Card Description": "Integrated", "Wireless Type": "802.11 A/C", "Number of USB 3.0 Ports": "1", "Brand Name": "HP", "Series": "Notebook 15-ay018nr", "Item model number": "X7W78UA#ABA", "Operating System": "Windows 10", "Item Weight": "4.8 pounds", "Product Dimensions": "10 x 15.1 x 0.9 inches", "Item Dimensions  L x W x H": "10.02 x 15.12 x 0.95 inches", "Processor Brand": "Intel", "Processor Count": "2", "Computer Memory Type": "DDR3 SDRAM", "Flash Memory Size": "256.0", "Optical Drive Type": "DVD+RW", "Batteries": "1 Lithium ion batteries required. (included)", "ASIN": "B01GFYP8II", "Customer Reviews": "", "Best Sellers Rank": "", "Shipping Weight": "6.1 pounds (", "Domestic Shipping": "Currently, item can be shipped only within the U.S. and to APO/FPO addresses. For APO/FPO shipments, please check with the manufacturer regarding warranty and support issues.", "International Shipping": "This item is not eligible for international shipping.", "Date First Available": "May 29, 2016", "Price": "$581.88", "Product Name": "HP 15-ay018nr 15.6-Inch Laptop (Intel Core i7, 8GB RAM, 256GB SSD)"},
{"Screen Size": "17.3 inches", "Max Screen Resolution": "1920x1080 pixels", "Processor": "2.6 GHz None", "RAM": "16 GB", "Memory Speed": "2133 MHz", "Hard Drive": "1000 GB flash_memory_solid_state", "Chipset Brand": "NVIDIA", "Card Description": "Dedicated", "Wireless Type": "802.11 A/C", "Number of USB 3.0 Ports": "3", "Brand Name": "Asus", "Series": "ROG", "Item model number": "GL702VM-DB74", "Operating System": "Windows 10", "Item Weight": "6 pounds", "Product Dimensions": "10.8 x 16.5 x 0.9 inches", "Item Dimensions  L x W x H": "10.8 x 16.5 x 0.9 inches", "Processor Brand": "Intel", "Processor Count": "4", "Computer Memory Type": "GDDR5", "Flash Memory Size": "256.0", "Hard Drive Rotational Speed": "7200 RPM", "Voltage": "19.5 volts", "Batteries": "1 Lithium ion batteries required. (included)", "ASIN": "B01KB0X0OQ", "Customer Reviews": "", "Best Sellers Rank": "", "Shipping Weight": "10.1 pounds (", "Domestic Shipping": "Currently, item can be shipped only within the U.S. and to APO/FPO addresses. For APO/FPO shipments, please check with the manufacturer regarding warranty and support issues.", "International Shipping": "This item is not eligible for international shipping.", "Date First Available": "August 17, 2016", "Price": "$1,449.00", "Product Name": "Asus ROG Strix GL702VM-DB74 17.3\" G-SYNC VR Ready Thin and Light Gaming Laptop NVIDIA GTX 1060 6GB Intel Core i7-6700HQ 16GB DDR4 256GB SSD + 1TB HDD"},
{"Screen Size": "17.3 inches", "Max Screen Resolution": "1920x1080 pixels", "Processor": "2.6 GHz Core i7 6700HQ", "RAM": "12 GB", "Hard Drive": "1000 GB SATA", "Chipset Brand": "NVIDIA", "Card Description": "Dedicated", "Graphics Card Ram Size": "6 MB", "Wireless Type": "802.11 A/C", "Number of USB 2.0 Ports": "1", "Number of USB 3.0 Ports": "2", "Brand Name": "MSI", "Series": "GE72", "Item model number": "GE72VR Apache Pro-024", "Hardware Platform": "PC", "Operating System": "Windows 10", "Item Weight": "6 pounds", "Product Dimensions": "16.5 x 11 x 1.1 inches", "Item Dimensions  L x W x H": "16.49 x 11.02 x 1.14 inches", "Processor Brand": "Intel", "Processor Count": "4", "Computer Memory Type": "GDDR5", "Flash Memory Size": "128.0", "Hard Drive Rotational Speed": "7200 RPM", "Optical Drive Type": "DVD-RW", "Voltage": "19.5 volts", "Batteries": "1 Lithium ion batteries required. (included)", "ASIN": "B01IS33JNK", "Customer Reviews": "", "Best Sellers Rank": "", "Shipping Weight": "11.9 pounds (", "Domestic Shipping": "Currently, item can be shipped only within the U.S. and to APO/FPO addresses. For APO/FPO shipments, please check with the manufacturer regarding warranty and support issues.", "International Shipping": "This item is not eligible for international shipping.", "Date First Available": "August 16, 2016", "Price": "$1,199.99", "Product Name": "MSI VR Ready GE72VR Apache Pro-024 17.3\" Powerful Gaming Laptop Geforce GTX 1060 i7-6700HQ 12GB 128GB M.2 SATA + 1TB Windows 10"},
{"Screen Size": "15.6 inches", "Max Screen Resolution": "1366 x 768 HD", "Processor": "2.1 GHz Intel Core i3", "RAM": "4 GB DDR3 SDRAM", "Hard Drive": "1 TB HDD 5400 rpm", "Graphics Coprocessor": "integrated_graphics", "Chipset Brand": "intel", "Card Description": "integrated", "Wireless Type": "802.11A, 802.11bgn, Bluetooth", "Brand Name": "Dell", "Series": "Dell 3000 series", "Item model number": "Dell i3558", "Hardware Platform": "PC", "Operating System": "Windows 10", "Item Weight": "7.2 pounds", "Product Dimensions": "15 x 10 x 0.9 inches", "Item Dimensions  L x W x H": "15 x 10 x 0.87 inches", "Color": "Black", "Processor Brand": "Intel\u00ae CoreTM i3-5015U", "Processor Count": "2", "Computer Memory Type": "DDR3 SDRAM", "Hard Drive Interface": "Serial ATA", "Hard Drive Rotational Speed": "5400 RPM", "Power Source": "AC & Battery", "ASIN": "B01KTUTMKO", "Customer Reviews": "", "Best Sellers Rank": "", "Shipping Weight": "7.2 pounds (", "Date First Available": "August 22, 2016", "Price": "$319.00", "Product Name": "2016 New Edition Dell Inspiron 3000 Premium 15.6 inch Laptop, Intel Core i3-5015U Processor 2.1GHz, 4GB RAM, 1TB HDD, HDMI, Bluetooth, No DVD, 802.11ac, HD Webcam, Windows 10 -MaxxAudio"},
{"Screen Size": "15.6 inches", "Screen Resolution": "1366x768", "Max Screen Resolution": "1366x768 pixels", "Processor": "2.5 GHz None", "RAM": "12 GB DDR4", "Hard Drive": "1000 GB SATA", "Graphics Coprocessor": "radeon r5", "Chipset Brand": "AMD Radeon R5 Graphics", "Card Description": "Integrated", "Wireless Type": "802.11 A/C", "Number of USB 2.0 Ports": "2", "Number of USB 3.0 Ports": "1", "Average Battery Life (in hours)": "5 hours", "Brand Name": "Lenovo", "Series": "ideapad 310", "Item model number": "ideapad 310 (80ST001NUS)", "Hardware Platform": "PC", "Operating System": "Windows 10", "Item Weight": "4.8 pounds", "Product Dimensions": "14.9 x 0.9 x 10.2 inches", "Item Dimensions  L x W x H": "14.92 x 0.9 x 10.24 inches", "Color": "Black", "Processor Brand": "AMD", "Processor Count": "4", "Computer Memory Type": "SDRAM", "Hard Drive Interface": "Serial ATA", "Hard Drive Rotational Speed": "5400 RPM", "Optical Drive Type": "DVD+RW", "Audio-out Ports (#)": "1", "Batteries": "1 Lithium Polymer batteries required. (included)", "ASIN": "B01LNOELA6", "Customer Reviews": "", "Best Sellers Rank": "", "Shipping Weight": "6.2 pounds (", "Domestic Shipping": "Currently, item can be shipped only within the U.S. and to APO/FPO addresses. For APO/FPO shipments, please check with the manufacturer regarding warranty and support issues.", "International Shipping": "This item is not eligible for international shipping.", "Date First Available": "October 4, 2016", "Price": "$486.42", "Product Name": "Lenovo Ideapad 310 15.6\" Laptop, Black (AMD A12-9700P, 12GB, 1TB HDD, AMD Radeon R5 Graphics, Windows 10) 80ST001NUS"},
{"Screen Size": "17.3 inches", "Screen Resolution": "1920 x 1080 pixels", "Max Screen Resolution": "1920*1080 pixels", "Processor": "2.6 GHz Intel Core i7", "RAM": "16 GB DDR4-SDRAM", "Memory Speed": "2133 MHz", "Hard Drive": "1 TB HDD", "Graphics Coprocessor": "NVIDIA GeForce GTX960M 2GB GDDR5", "Chipset Brand": "NVIDIA GeForce", "Card Description": "dedicated", "Graphics Card Ram Size": "2048 MB", "Wireless Type": "802.11 A/C", "Number of USB 3.0 Ports": "1", "Brand Name": "Asus", "Series": "ROG GL752VW", "Item model number": "GL752VW-DH71", "Hardware Platform": "PC", "Operating System": "Windows 10", "Item Weight": "6.6 pounds", "Product Dimensions": "10.6 x 16.6 x 1.3 inches", "Item Dimensions  L x W x H": "10.6 x 16.6 x 1.3 inches", "Color": "Metallic", "Processor Brand": "Intel", "Processor Count": "4", "Computer Memory Type": "GDDR5", "Flash Memory Size": "16 GB", "Hard Drive Interface": "Serial ATA-600", "Hard Drive Rotational Speed": "7200 RPM", "Optical Drive Type": "DL DVD\u00b1RW/CD-RW", "Power Source": "Corded-Electric, Battery", "Batteries": "1 Lithium ion batteries required. (included)", "ASIN": "B01578ZK9A", "Customer Reviews": "", "Best Sellers Rank": "", "Shipping Weight": "10.6 pounds (", "Domestic Shipping": "Currently, item can be shipped only within the U.S. and to APO/FPO addresses. For APO/FPO shipments, please check with the manufacturer regarding warranty and support issues.", "International Shipping": "This item can be shipped to select countries outside of the U.S.", "Date First Available": "October 9, 2015", "Price": "$1,021.98", "Product Name": "ASUS ROG GL752VW-DH71 17.3-inch Gaming Laptop (Intel i7 2.6GHz, 16GB DDR4 RAM, 1TB HDD,  GTX960M 2GB Graphic Card, Windows 10)"},
{"Screen Size": "15.6 inches", "Screen Resolution": "1920 x 1080 pixels", "Max Screen Resolution": "1920*1080 pixels", "Processor": "2.6 GHz Intel Core i7", "RAM": "16 GB DDR4-SDRAM", "Memory Speed": "2133 MHz", "Hard Drive": "128 GB SSD; HDD", "Graphics Coprocessor": "NVIDIA GTX960M 4GB GDDR5", "Chipset Brand": "NVIDIA GeForce", "Card Description": "dedicated", "Graphics Card Ram Size": "4096 MB", "Wireless Type": "802.11 A/C", "Number of USB 2.0 Ports": "1", "Number of USB 3.0 Ports": "2", "Brand Name": "Asus", "Series": "ROG GL552VW", "Item model number": "GL552VW-DH74", "Hardware Platform": "PC", "Operating System": "Windows 10", "Item Weight": "5.6 pounds", "Product Dimensions": "10.1 x 15.1 x 1.3 inches", "Item Dimensions  L x W x H": "10.1 x 15.1 x 1.3 inches", "Color": "Metallic", "Processor Brand": "Intel", "Processor Count": "4", "Computer Memory Type": "GDDR5", "Flash Memory Size": "128", "Hard Drive Rotational Speed": "7200 RPM", "Optical Drive Type": "DL DVD\u00b1RW/CD-RW", "Voltage": "19 volts", "Batteries": "1 Lithium ion batteries required. (included)", "ASIN": "B015ZG997I", "Customer Reviews": "", "Best Sellers Rank": "", "Shipping Weight": "9.3 pounds (", "Domestic Shipping": "Currently, item can be shipped only within the U.S. and to APO/FPO addresses. For APO/FPO shipments, please check with the manufacturer regarding warranty and support issues.", "International Shipping": "This item is not eligible for international shipping.", "Date First Available": "October 9, 2015", "Price": "$1,112.92", "Product Name": "ASUS ROG GL552VW-DH74 15-Inch Gaming Laptop, Discrete GPU GeForce GTX 960M 4GB VRAM, 16GB DDR4, 1TB, 128GB SSD (ROG Metallic)"},
{"Screen Size": "13.5 inches", "Max Screen Resolution": "3000*2000 pixels", "Processor": "2.1 GHz Core M Family", "RAM": "8 GB DDR3", "Hard Drive": "128 GB", "Graphics Coprocessor": "Intel HD", "Card Description": "integrated", "Wireless Type": "802.11 A/C", "Number of USB 3.0 Ports": "2", "Brand Name": "Microsoft", "Series": "CR9-00001", "Item model number": "CR9-00001", "Operating System": "Windows 10", "Item Weight": "3.5 pounds", "Product Dimensions": "10.9 x 16.5 x 1.9 inches", "Item Dimensions  L x W x H": "10.95 x 16.46 x 1.93 inches", "Color": "silver", "Processor Brand": "Intel", "Processor Count": "1", "Flash Memory Size": "128 GB", "Power Source": "Battery", "Batteries": "1 Lithium ion batteries required. (included)", "ASIN": "B0163GQJOU", "Customer Reviews": "", "Best Sellers Rank": "", "Shipping Weight": "8.8 pounds (", "Domestic Shipping": "Currently, item can be shipped only within the U.S. and to APO/FPO addresses. For APO/FPO shipments, please check with the manufacturer regarding warranty and support issues.", "International Shipping": "This item is not eligible for international shipping.", "Date First Available": "October 6, 2015", "Price": "$1,228.84", "Product Name": "Microsoft Surface Book (128 GB, 8 GB RAM, Intel Core i5)"},
{"Screen Size": "14 inches", "Max Screen Resolution": "1920x1080 pixels", "Processor": "1.83 GHz Intel Celeron", "RAM": "4 GB SDRAM", "Hard Drive": "16 GB emmc", "Card Description": "integrated", "Wireless Type": "802.11 A/C", "Number of USB 3.0 Ports": "1", "Brand Name": "HP", "Series": "Chromebook", "Item model number": "14-ak050nr", "Operating System": "Chrome", "Item Weight": "3.7 pounds", "Product Dimensions": "9.4 x 13.5 x 0.7 inches", "Item Dimensions  L x W x H": "9.45 x 13.54 x 0.7 inches", "Color": "White", "Processor Brand": "Intel", "Processor Count": "1", "Flash Memory Size": "16.0", "Batteries": "1 Lithium ion batteries required. (included)", "ASIN": "B015ZD71P8", "Customer Reviews": "", "Best Sellers Rank": "", "Shipping Weight": "5.2 pounds (", "Domestic Shipping": "Currently, item can be shipped only within the U.S. and to APO/FPO addresses. For APO/FPO shipments, please check with the manufacturer regarding warranty and support issues.", "International Shipping": "This item is not eligible for international shipping.", "Date First Available": "November 8, 2015", "Product Name": "HP Chromebook 14-ak050nr 14-Inch Laptop (Intel Celeron, 4 GB RAM, 16 GB SSD)"},
{"Screen Size": "15.6 inches", "Screen Resolution": "1366x768", "Max Screen Resolution": "1366x768", "Processor": "1.6 GHz Intel Celeron", "RAM": "4 GB SDRAM DDR3", "Hard Drive": "500 GB mechanical_hard_drive", "Graphics Coprocessor": "integrated_graphics", "Chipset Brand": "intel", "Card Description": "integrated", "Wireless Type": "802.11 B/G, 802.11bgn, 802.11B", "Average Battery Life (in hours)": "3 hours", "Brand Name": "Lenovo", "Series": "Lenovo", "Hardware Platform": "PC", "Operating System": "windows 10", "Item Weight": "5.6 pounds", "Product Dimensions": "15 x 11 x 1 inches", "Item Dimensions  L x W x H": "15 x 11 x 1 inches", "Color": "Black", "Processor Brand": "Intel", "Processor Count": "2", "Computer Memory Type": "DDR3 SDRAM", "Hard Drive Interface": "Serial ATA", "Hard Drive Rotational Speed": "5400 RPM", "ASIN": "B01MQHADBT", "Customer Reviews": "", "Best Sellers Rank": "", "Shipping Weight": "6 pounds (", "Date First Available": "November 11, 2016", "Price": "$240.00", "Product Name": "2017 Newest Lenovo Premium Built High Performance 15.6 inch HD Laptop (Intel Celeron Processor 4GB RAM 500GB HDD, DVD RW, Bluetooth, Webcam, WiFi, HDMI, Windows 10 ) - Black"},
{"Screen Size": "15.6 inches", "Screen Resolution": "1366x768", "Max Screen Resolution": "1366 x 768", "Processor": "2.16 GHz Intel Celeron", "RAM": "4 GB SDRAM DDR3", "Memory Speed": "1600 MHz", "Hard Drive": "500 GB HDD 7200 rpm", "Graphics Coprocessor": "integrated graphics", "Chipset Brand": "Intel", "Card Description": "integrated", "Wireless Type": "Bluetooth, 802.11bgn", "Average Battery Life (in hours)": "3 hours", "Brand Name": "Lenovo IdeaPad", "Series": "ideapad", "Item model number": "ideapad", "Hardware Platform": "PC", "Operating System": "Windows 10", "Item Weight": "4.3 pounds", "Product Dimensions": "14.9 x 10.4 x 0.9 inches", "Item Dimensions  L x W x H": "14.88 x 10.43 x 0.89 inches", "Color": "Black", "Processor Brand": "Intel", "Processor Count": "2", "Computer Memory Type": "DDR3 SDRAM", "Hard Drive Interface": "Serial ATA", "Hard Drive Rotational Speed": "5400.00", "Optical Drive Type": "DVD+RW", "Power Source": "AC", "ASIN": "B01JFJJ5NE", "Customer Reviews": "", "Best Sellers Rank": "", "Shipping Weight": "6 pounds (", "Date First Available": "February 4, 2016", "Price": "$239.96", "Product Name": "Lenovo IdeaPad 15.6 Inch HD Laptop (Intel Dual-Core Celeron N3060 1.6 GHz Processor, 4GB RAM, 500GB HDD, DVD RW, Bluetooth, Webcam, WiFi, HDMI, Windows 10) Black"},
{"Screen Size": "17.3 inches", "Screen Resolution": "1920 x 1080 pixels", "Max Screen Resolution": "1920*1080 pixels", "Processor": "2.6 GHz Intel Core i7", "RAM": "16 GB DDR4-SDRAM", "Memory Speed": "2133 MHz", "Hard Drive": "128 GB SSD; HDD", "Graphics Coprocessor": "NVIDIA GeForce GTX960M 4GB GDDR5", "Chipset Brand": "NVIDIA GeForce", "Card Description": "dedicated", "Graphics Card Ram Size": "4096 MB", "Wireless Type": "802.11 A/C", "Number of USB 2.0 Ports": "2", "Number of USB 3.0 Ports": "3", "Brand Name": "Asus", "Series": "ROG GL752VW", "Item model number": "GL752VW-DH74", "Hardware Platform": "PC", "Operating System": "Windows 10", "Item Weight": "6.6 pounds", "Product Dimensions": "10.6 x 16.3 x 1.3 inches", "Item Dimensions  L x W x H": "10.6 x 16.3 x 1.3 inches", "Color": "Metallic", "Processor Brand": "Intel", "Processor Count": "4", "Computer Memory Type": "GDDR5", "Flash Memory Size": "128", "Hard Drive Rotational Speed": "7200 RPM", "Optical Drive Type": "DL DVD\u00b1RW/CD-RW", "Power Source": "Battery", "Batteries": "1 Lithium ion batteries required. (included)", "ASIN": "B015ZG9964", "Customer Reviews": "", "Best Sellers Rank": "", "Shipping Weight": "10.2 pounds (", "Domestic Shipping": "Currently, item can be shipped only within the U.S. and to APO/FPO addresses. For APO/FPO shipments, please check with the manufacturer regarding warranty and support issues.", "International Shipping": "This item is not eligible for international shipping.", "Date First Available": "October 9, 2015", "Price": "$999.99", "Product Name": "ASUS ROG GL752VW-DH74 17-Inch Gaming Laptop, Discrete GPU GeForce GTX 960M 4 GB VRAM, 16GB DDR4, 1 TB, 128 GB SSD (ROG Metallic)"},
{"Screen Size": "15.6 inches", "Screen Resolution": "1360x768", "Max Screen Resolution": "1366 x 768", "Processor": "2.1 GHz Intel Core i3", "RAM": "4 GB SDRAM DDR3", "Hard Drive": "1 TB HDD 5400 rpm", "Graphics Coprocessor": "integrated_graphics", "Chipset Brand": "intel", "Card Description": "integrated", "Wireless Type": "802.11 A/C, 802.11A", "Average Battery Life (in hours)": "8 hours", "Brand Name": "Dell", "Series": "Inspiron 3000", "Item model number": "Inspiron 3000", "Hardware Platform": "PC", "Operating System": "Windows 10", "Item Weight": "4.8 ounces", "Product Dimensions": "15 x 10.2 x 0.9 inches", "Item Dimensions  L x W x H": "15 x 10.2 x 0.9 inches", "Processor Brand": "Intel", "Processor Count": "2", "Computer Memory Type": "DDR3 SDRAM", "Hard Drive Interface": "Serial ATA", "Hard Drive Rotational Speed": "5400 RPM", "Power Source": "AC & Battery", "ASIN": "B01KVZV52A", "Customer Reviews": "", "Best Sellers Rank": "", "Shipping Weight": "7.2 pounds (", "Date First Available": "August 23, 2016", "Price": "$317.00", "Product Name": "2016 New Edition Dell Inspiron 15.6\" HD Display Premium High Performance Laptop PC, Intel Core i3-5015U 2.1 GHz Processor, 4GB RAM, 1TB HDD, HDMI, Bluetooth, WIFI, Webcam, MaxxAudio, Windows 10, Black"},
{"Screen Size": "15 inches", "Screen Resolution": "1920 x 1080 pixels", "Max Screen Resolution": "1920 x 1080 pixels", "Processor": "2.5 GHz Intel Core i7", "RAM": "8 GB DDR3", "Hard Drive": "256 GB SSD", "Graphics Coprocessor": "Shared", "Chipset Brand": "intel", "Card Description": "integrated", "Wireless Type": "802.11 A/C", "Number of USB 3.0 Ports": "2", "Brand Name": "Samsung", "Series": "Notebook 9 15\"", "Item model number": "NP900X5L-K02US", "Operating System": "Windows 10 Home", "Item Weight": "2.8 pounds", "Product Dimensions": "13.6 x 9.3 x 0.6 inches", "Item Dimensions  L x W x H": "13.6 x 9.32 x 0.57 inches", "Color": "Iron Silver", "Processor Brand": "Intel", "Processor Count": "1", "Computer Memory Type": "DDR3 SDRAM", "Flash Memory Size": "256.0", "Hard Drive Rotational Speed": "1 RPM", "Optical Drive Type": "No", "Battery Type": "Lithium Polymer (LiPo)", "Batteries": "1 Lithium Polymer batteries required. (included)", "ASIN": "B01AWGXNH8", "Customer Reviews": "", "Best Sellers Rank": "", "Shipping Weight": "4.8 pounds (", "Domestic Shipping": "Currently, item can be shipped only within the U.S. and to APO/FPO addresses. For APO/FPO shipments, please check with the manufacturer regarding warranty and support issues.", "International Shipping": "This item is not eligible for international shipping.", "Date First Available": "February 15, 2016", "Price": "$1,074.99", "Product Name": "Samsung NP900X5L-K02US Notebook 9 15\" Laptop (Iron Silver)"},
{"Screen Size": "14 inches", "Max Screen Resolution": "1920x1080 pixels", "Processor": "1.6 GHz Intel Celeron", "RAM": "4 GB DDR3 SDRAM", "Hard Drive": "32 GB", "Chipset Brand": "intel", "Card Description": "Integrated", "Wireless Type": "802.11 A/C", "Number of USB 3.0 Ports": "2", "Average Battery Life (in hours)": "12 hours", "Brand Name": "Acer", "Series": "CB3-431", "Item model number": "CB3-431-C0AK", "Operating System": "Chrome", "Item Weight": "3.4 pounds", "Product Dimensions": "9.3 x 13.4 x 0.7 inches", "Item Dimensions  L x W x H": "9.31 x 13.43 x 0.67 inches", "Color": "Luxury Gold", "Processor Brand": "Intel", "Processor Count": "1", "Flash Memory Size": "32.0", "Batteries": "1 Lithium Polymer batteries required. (included)", "ASIN": "B01J42JMQ2", "Customer Reviews": "", "Best Sellers Rank": "", "Shipping Weight": "5.1 pounds (", "Domestic Shipping": "Currently, item can be shipped only within the U.S. and to APO/FPO addresses. For APO/FPO shipments, please check with the manufacturer regarding warranty and support issues.", "International Shipping": "This item can be shipped to select countries outside of the U.S.", "Date First Available": "September 4, 2016", "Price": "$299.99", "Product Name": "Acer Chromebook 14, Aluminum, 14-inch Full HD, Intel Celeron N3160, 4GB LPDDR3, 32GB, Chrome, Gold, CB3-431-C0AK"},
{"Screen Size": "13.3 inches", "Processor": "2.1 GHz Intel Core 2 Duo Mobile", "RAM": "2 GB ddr2_sdram", "Hard Drive": "120 GB mechanical_hard_drive", "Graphics Coprocessor": "integrated_graphics", "Chipset Brand": "intel", "Card Description": "integrated", "Wireless Type": "802.11n", "Number of USB 2.0 Ports": "2", "Brand Name": "Apple", "Series": "Model A1181", "Item model number": "MB403B/A", "Hardware Platform": "Mac", "Operating System": "Mac OS x 10.7 Lion", "Item Weight": "5.1 pounds", "Product Dimensions": "12.8 x 8.9 x 1.1 inches", "Item Dimensions  L x W x H": "12.8 x 8.94 x 1.08 inches", "Color": "White", "Processor Brand": "Intel", "Processor Count": "2", "Computer Memory Type": "DDR2 SDRAM", "Flash Memory Size": "512", "ASIN": "B00159LRXY", "Customer Reviews": "", "Best Sellers Rank": "", "Shipping Weight": "8.9 pounds", "Date First Available": "September 14, 2013", "Product Name": "Apple A1181 Macbook MB403LL 13.3 Inch Laptop (2.1 GHz Intel Core 2 Duo Mobile, 2 GB SDRAM, 120GB HDD, Mac OS x 10.7 Lion), White"},
{"Screen Size": "11.6 inches", "Max Screen Resolution": "1366x768 pixels", "Processor": "1.6 GHz Celeron N3150", "RAM": "2 GB DDR3L SDRAM", "Hard Drive": "flash_memory_solid_state", "Graphics Coprocessor": "Integrated Graphics", "Chipset Brand": "Intel", "Card Description": "Integrated", "Wireless Type": "802.11bgn", "Number of USB 3.0 Ports": "1", "Brand Name": "Dell", "Series": "Inspiron 11 3000", "Item model number": "i3168-0028BLU", "Hardware Platform": "PC", "Operating System": "Windows 10 Microsoft Signature Image", "Item Weight": "3.2 pounds", "Product Dimensions": "11.3 x 0.8 x 7.8 inches", "Item Dimensions  L x W x H": "11.3 x 0.8 x 7.8 inches", "Color": "Bali Blue", "Processor Brand": "Intel", "Processor Count": "2", "Computer Memory Type": "DDR3 SDRAM", "Flash Memory Size": "32", "Optical Drive Type": "None", "Batteries": "1 Lithium ion batteries required. (included)", "ASIN": "B01F3R9136", "Customer Reviews": "", "Best Sellers Rank": "", "Shipping Weight": "3.6 pounds (", "Domestic Shipping": "Currently, item can be shipped only within the U.S. and to APO/FPO addresses. For APO/FPO shipments, please check with the manufacturer regarding warranty and support issues.", "International Shipping": "This item is not eligible for international shipping.", "Date First Available": "May 18, 2016", "Price": "$216.70", "Product Name": "Dell i3168-0028BLU 11.6\" HD 2-in-1 Laptop (Intel Celeron N3060 1.6GHz Processor, 2 GB DDR3L SDRAM, 32 GB SDD, Windows 10 Microsoft Signature Image) Bali Blue"},
{"Screen Size": "14 inches", "Max Screen Resolution": "1920x1080 pixels", "Processor": "2.6 GHz Intel Core i7", "RAM": "16 GB", "Hard Drive": "256 GB flash_memory_solid_state", "Chipset Brand": "nvidia", "Card Description": "Dedicated", "Wireless Type": "802.11 A/G", "Number of USB 3.0 Ports": "3", "Brand Name": "Razer", "Series": "B5", "Item model number": "RZ09-01952E71-R3U1", "Operating System": "Windows 10", "Item Weight": "4.2 pounds", "Product Dimensions": "13.6 x 0.7 x 9.3 inches", "Item Dimensions  L x W x H": "13.6 x 0.7 x 9.3 inches", "Processor Brand": "Intel", "Processor Count": "4", "Computer Memory Type": "DDR SDRAM", "Batteries": "1 Lithium ion batteries required. (included)", "ASIN": "B01LZ1MIO6", "Customer Reviews": "", "Best Sellers Rank": "", "Shipping Weight": "8.4 pounds (", "Domestic Shipping": "Currently, item can be shipped only within the U.S. and to APO/FPO addresses. For APO/FPO shipments, please check with the manufacturer regarding warranty and support issues.", "International Shipping": "This item is not eligible for international shipping.", "Date First Available": "September 22, 2016", "Price": "$1,799.99", "Product Name": "The Razer Blade (GeForce GTX 1060) 14\" HD Gaming Laptop (6th Gen Intel Core i7, 16GB RAM, 256GB SSD) - VR Ready"},
{"Screen Size": "15.6 inches", "Screen Resolution": "1366x768", "Max Screen Resolution": "1366 x 768", "Processor": "2.3 GHz Intel Core i3", "RAM": "8 GB SDRAM DDR3", "Memory Speed": "2133 MHz", "Hard Drive": "1 TB HDD 5400 rpm", "Graphics Coprocessor": "Intel Integrated Graphics", "Chipset Brand": "intel", "Card Description": "integrated", "Wireless Type": "802.11bgn, Bluetooth", "Number of USB 2.0 Ports": "2", "Average Battery Life (in hours)": "6.5 hours", "Brand Name": "HP", "Series": "Hp 15-ay091", "Item model number": "Hp 15", "Hardware Platform": "PC", "Operating System": "Windows 10", "Item Weight": "4.7 pounds", "Product Dimensions": "15.1 x 10 x 0.9 inches", "Item Dimensions  L x W x H": "15.12 x 10.02 x 0.95 inches", "Color": "Turbo Silver", "Processor Brand": "Intel", "Processor Count": "2", "Computer Memory Type": "DDR3 SDRAM", "Hard Drive Interface": "Serial ATA", "Hard Drive Rotational Speed": "5400 RPM", "Power Source": "AC & Battery", "ASIN": "B01L8K38MM", "Customer Reviews": "", "Best Sellers Rank": "", "Shipping Weight": "6.2 pounds (", "Date First Available": "August 2, 2016", "Price": "$375.00", "Product Name": "2016 Newest HP Pavilion 15.6\" Touchscreen Premium High Performance Laptop, Intel Core i3-6100U 2.3 GHz, 8GB RAM, 1TB HDD, DVD+/RW, WIFI, Webcam, Bluetooth, Windows 10"},
{"Screen Size": "15.6 inches", "Max Screen Resolution": "1366 x 768 HD", "Processor": "2 GHz Intel Core i3", "RAM": "6 GB DDR3 SDRAM", "Hard Drive": "1 TB HDD 5400 rpm", "Graphics Coprocessor": "integrated_graphics", "Chipset Brand": "intel", "Card Description": "integrated", "Wireless Type": "802.11A, 802.11bgn, Bluetooth", "Brand Name": "Dell", "Series": "Dell 3000 series", "Item model number": "Dell i3558", "Hardware Platform": "PC", "Operating System": "Windows 10", "Item Weight": "7.1 pounds", "Product Dimensions": "15 x 10 x 0.9 inches", "Item Dimensions  L x W x H": "15 x 10 x 0.87 inches", "Color": "Black", "Processor Brand": "Intel\u00ae CoreTM i3-5005U", "Processor Count": "2", "Computer Memory Type": "DDR3 SDRAM", "Hard Drive Interface": "Serial ATA", "Hard Drive Rotational Speed": "5400 RPM", "Power Source": "AC & Battery", "ASIN": "B01N6ARNOS", "Customer Reviews": "", "Best Sellers Rank": "", "Shipping Weight": "7.1 pounds (", "Date First Available": "November 29, 2016", "Price": "$330.00", "Product Name": "2017 New Edition Dell Inspiron 3000 Premium High Performance 15.6\u201d HD Laptop, Intel Core i3 Processor 2GHz, 6GB RAM, 1TB HDD, HDMI, Bluetooth, DVD, 802.11ac, Webcam, Windows 10 -MaxxAudio"},
{"Screen Size": "13.3 inches", "Max Screen Resolution": "1366 x 768", "Processor": "2.3 GHz Intel Core i3", "RAM": "6 GB SDRAM DDR3", "Hard Drive": "500 GB HDD 5400 rpm", "Graphics Coprocessor": "integrated_graphics", "Chipset Brand": "intel", "Card Description": "integrated", "Wireless Type": "802.11 B/G, 802.11 A/C, 802.11bgn, 802.11B", "Brand Name": "HP", "Series": "x360", "Item model number": "x360", "Hardware Platform": "PC", "Operating System": "Windows 10", "Item Weight": "3.7 pounds", "Product Dimensions": "12.8 x 8.7 x 0.8 inches", "Item Dimensions  L x W x H": "12.8 x 8.7 x 0.8 inches", "Color": "Silver", "Processor Brand": "Intel", "Processor Count": "2", "Computer Memory Type": "DDR3 SDRAM", "Hard Drive Interface": "Serial ATA", "Hard Drive Rotational Speed": "5400 RPM", "ASIN": "B01L21KHG2", "Customer Reviews": "", "Best Sellers Rank": "", "Shipping Weight": "5.2 pounds (", "Date First Available": "August 26, 2016", "Price": "$478.88", "Product Name": "2016 Newest HP Pavilion x360 High Performance 13.3\" 2-in-1 Touchscreen Convertible IPS Laptop, Intel Core i3-6100U Processor, 6GB RAM, 500GB HDD, HDMI, Bluetooth, No DVD, 802.11ac, Webcam, Windows 10"},
{"Screen Size": "13.3 inches", "Max Screen Resolution": "1366x768 pixels", "Processor": "1.6 GHz None", "RAM": "4 GB DDR3 SDRAM", "Hard Drive": "Flash Memory Solid State", "Graphics Coprocessor": "integrated_graphics", "Chipset Brand": "intel", "Card Description": "Integrated", "Wireless Type": "802.11 A/C", "Number of USB 3.0 Ports": "3", "Brand Name": "Asus", "Item model number": "C300SA-DH02-RD", "Operating System": "Chrome", "Item Weight": "3.1 pounds", "Product Dimensions": "9.1 x 13 x 0.8 inches", "Item Dimensions  L x W x H": "9.1 x 13 x 0.8 inches", "Color": "Red", "Processor Brand": "Intel", "Processor Count": "2", "Flash Memory Size": "16.0", "Optical Drive Type": "None", "Batteries": "1 Lithium ion batteries required. (included)", "ASIN": "B01M72MG4V", "Customer Reviews": "", "Best Sellers Rank": "", "Shipping Weight": "4.7 pounds (", "Domestic Shipping": "Currently, item can be shipped only within the U.S. and to APO/FPO addresses. For APO/FPO shipments, please check with the manufacturer regarding warranty and support issues.", "International Shipping": "This item can be shipped to select countries outside of the U.S.", "Date First Available": "October 19, 2016", "Price": "$209.00", "Product Name": "ASUS 13.3-inch Red Chromebook [C300AS] Intel Celeron N3060 1.6GHz Processor, 4GB 1866MHz DDR3 Memory, 16GB Flash Storage, HDMI, USB 3.0, SD Card, 15-hour Battery-Life, 802.11AC WiFi"},
{"Screen Size": "13.3 inches", "Screen Resolution": "2560 x 1600", "Max Screen Resolution": "2560x1600 pixels", "Processor": "2.7 GHz Intel Core i5", "RAM": "8 GB LPDDR3", "Memory Speed": "1866 MHz", "Hard Drive": "flash_memory_solid_state", "Graphics Coprocessor": "Intel Iris Graphics 6100", "Chipset Brand": "intel", "Card Description": "integrated", "Wireless Type": "802.11A, 802.11 A/C, 802.11B, 802.11G, 802.11n", "Number of USB 3.0 Ports": "2", "Average Battery Life (in hours)": "7 hours", "Brand Name": "Apple", "Series": "A1278", "Item model number": "MF839LL/A", "Hardware Platform": "Mac", "Operating System": "Mac OS X", "Item Weight": "3.5 pounds", "Product Dimensions": "8.6 x 12.3 x 0.7 inches", "Item Dimensions  L x W x H": "8.62 x 12.35 x 0.71 inches", "Color": "Silver", "Processor Brand": "Intel", "Processor Count": "1", "Computer Memory Type": "DDR3 SDRAM", "Flash Memory Size": "128", "Optical Drive Type": "No", "Audio-out Ports (#)": "1", "Battery Type": "Lithium Polymer (LiPo)", "Power Source": "AC", "Batteries": "1 Lithium Metal batteries required.", "ASIN": "B00UGBMRQ8", "Customer Reviews": "", "Best Sellers Rank": "", "Shipping Weight": "5.5 pounds", "Domestic Shipping": "Currently, item can be shipped only within the U.S. and to APO/FPO addresses. For APO/FPO shipments, please check with the manufacturer regarding warranty and support issues.", "International Shipping": "This item is not eligible for international shipping.", "Date First Available": "March 9, 2015", "Product Name": "Apple MacBook Pro MF839LL/A 13.3-Inch Laptop with Retina Display (2.7 GHz Intel Core i5 Processor, 8 GB RAM, 128 GB Hard Drive, OS X Yosemite)"},
{"Screen Size": "11.6 inches", "Max Screen Resolution": "1366x768 pixels", "Processor": "1.6 GHz 8032", "RAM": "4 GB LPDDR3", "Hard Drive": "16 GB Flash Memory Solid State", "Chipset Brand": "Intel", "Card Description": "Integrated", "Wireless Type": "802.11 A/C", "Number of USB 3.0 Ports": "2", "Average Battery Life (in hours)": "10 hours", "Brand Name": "Lenovo", "Series": "4540203", "Item model number": "80VH0001US", "Hardware Platform": "Chrome", "Operating System": "Chrome", "Item Weight": "2.7 pounds", "Product Dimensions": "8.2 x 11.8 x 0.9 inches", "Item Dimensions  L x W x H": "8.2 x 11.8 x 0.9 inches", "Color": "na", "Processor Brand": "Intel", "Processor Count": "1", "Flash Memory Size": "16.0", "Optical Drive Type": "None", "Batteries": "1 Lithium ion batteries required. (included)", "ASIN": "B01H5EFSJQ", "Customer Reviews": "", "Best Sellers Rank": "", "Shipping Weight": "4.1 pounds (", "Domestic Shipping": "Amazon only ships this item within the contiguous 48 United States. Other Sellers on Amazon may ship this item to Alaska, Hawaii and US Territories.", "International Shipping": "This item is not eligible for international shipping.", "Date First Available": "June 16, 2016", "Price": "$205.00", "Product Name": "Lenovo Chromebook N22 11.6\" Notebook, IPS Touchscreen, Intel N3060 Dual-Core, 16GB eMMC SSD, 4GB DDR3, 802.11ac, Bluetooth, ChromeOS"},
{"Screen Size": "15.6 inches", "Screen Resolution": "1366x768", "Max Screen Resolution": "1376 x 768", "Processor": "2.5 GHz Intel Core i5", "RAM": "6 GB SDRAM DDR3", "Memory Speed": "1600 MHz", "Hard Drive": "500 GB HDD 5400 rpm", "Graphics Coprocessor": "Radeon", "Chipset Brand": "amd", "Card Description": "integrated", "Wireless Type": "802.11bgn", "Number of USB 2.0 Ports": "2", "Average Battery Life (in hours)": "5 hours", "Brand Name": "Dell", "Series": "inspiron", "Item model number": "i5555", "Hardware Platform": "PC", "Operating System": "Windows 10", "Item Weight": "5.4 pounds", "Product Dimensions": "14.9 x 10.3 x 1 inches", "Item Dimensions  L x W x H": "14.9 x 10.3 x 1 inches", "Color": "BLACK", "Processor Brand": "AMD", "Processor Count": "4", "Computer Memory Type": "DDR3 SDRAM", "Hard Drive Interface": "Serial ATA", "Hard Drive Rotational Speed": "5400 RPM", "Power Source": "AC & Battery", "ASIN": "B01IWXJQVA", "Customer Reviews": "", "Best Sellers Rank": "", "Shipping Weight": "7.2 pounds (", "Date First Available": "May 18, 2016", "Price": "$304.45", "Product Name": "Dell Inspiron i5555 Premium Laptop PC (2016 Newest Model), 15.6-inch HD LED-backlit Display, AMD A8-7410 Quad Core Processor, 6GB DDR3L RAM, 500GB HDD, DVD +/- RW, Radeon R5 Graphics, Windows 10"},
{"Screen Size": "15.6 inches", "Screen Resolution": "1920 x 1080 pixels", "Max Screen Resolution": "1920x1080 pixels", "Processor": "2.6 GHz Intel Core i7", "RAM": "8 GB DDR4 SDRAM", "Hard Drive": "1 TB mechanical_hard_drive", "Graphics Coprocessor": "NVIDIA GeForce GTX 960M", "Chipset Brand": "NVIDIA GeForce GTX 960M", "Card Description": "dedicated", "Graphics Card Ram Size": "4000 MB", "Wireless Type": "802.11 A/C", "Number of USB 2.0 Ports": "1", "Number of USB 3.0 Ports": "2", "Average Battery Life (in hours)": "4 hours", "Brand Name": "Lenovo", "Series": "Y700", "Item model number": "80NV0026US", "Operating System": "Windows 10", "Item Weight": "5.7 pounds", "Product Dimensions": "15.2 x 1 x 10.9 inches", "Item Dimensions  L x W x H": "15.24 x 1.02 x 10.91 inches", "Color": "Black", "Processor Brand": "Intel", "Processor Count": "4", "Flash Memory Size": "8 GB", "Hard Drive Rotational Speed": "5400 RPM", "Optical Drive Type": "None", "Power Source": "Corded-Electric, Battery", "Batteries": "1 Lithium Polymer batteries required. (included)", "ASIN": "B014MIBR7K", "Customer Reviews": "", "Best Sellers Rank": "", "Shipping Weight": "10.6 pounds (", "Domestic Shipping": "Currently, item can be shipped only within the U.S. and to APO/FPO addresses. For APO/FPO shipments, please check with the manufacturer regarding warranty and support issues.", "International Shipping": "This item is not eligible for international shipping.", "Date First Available": "September 15, 2015", "Price": "$889.16", "Product Name": "Lenovo Y700 - 15.6 Inch Full HD Gaming Laptop (Intel Core i7, 8 GB RAM, 1TB HDD, NVIDIA GeForce GTX 960M, Windows 10) 80NV0026US"},
{"Screen Size": "14 inches", "Max Screen Resolution": "1920x1080 pixels", "Processor": "1.83 GHz Intel Celeron", "RAM": "4 GB SDRAM", "Hard Drive": "16 GB flash_memory_solid_state", "Card Description": "integrated", "Wireless Type": "802.11 A/C", "Number of USB 3.0 Ports": "1", "Brand Name": "HP", "Series": "Chromebook", "Item model number": "14-ak060nr", "Operating System": "Chrome", "Item Weight": "3.7 pounds", "Product Dimensions": "9.4 x 13.5 x 0.7 inches", "Item Dimensions  L x W x H": "9.45 x 13.54 x 0.7 inches", "Color": "White", "Processor Brand": "Intel", "Processor Count": "1", "Flash Memory Size": "16.0", "Batteries": "1 Lithium ion batteries required. (included)", "ASIN": "B0178J9S6C", "Customer Reviews": "", "Best Sellers Rank": "", "Shipping Weight": "5.2 pounds (", "Domestic Shipping": "Currently, item can be shipped only within the U.S. and to APO/FPO addresses. For APO/FPO shipments, please check with the manufacturer regarding warranty and support issues.", "International Shipping": "This item is not eligible for international shipping.", "Date First Available": "November 8, 2015", "Product Name": "HP Chromebook 14-ak060nr 14-Inch Laptop (Intel Celeron, 4 GB RAM, 16 GB SSD)"},
{"Screen Size": "15.4 inches", "Screen Resolution": "2880 x 1800", "Max Screen Resolution": "2880x1800 pixels", "Processor": "2.6 GHz Intel Core i7", "RAM": "16 GB LPDDR3", "Hard Drive": "256 GB", "Graphics Coprocessor": "Intel HD Graphics 530", "Chipset Brand": "intel", "Card Description": "integrated", "Brand Name": "Apple", "Series": "MacBook Pro", "Item model number": "MLW72LL/A", "Hardware Platform": "Mac", "Operating System": "Mac OS Sierra", "Item Weight": "4 pounds", "Product Dimensions": "9.5 x 13.8 x 0.6 inches", "Item Dimensions  L x W x H": "9.48 x 13.75 x 0.61 inches", "Color": "Silver", "Processor Brand": "Intel", "Processor Count": "1", "Battery Type": "Lithium Polymer (LiPo)", "ASIN": "B01LTHXAO0", "Customer Reviews": "", "Best Sellers Rank": "", "Shipping Weight": "7.5 pounds (", "Domestic Shipping": "Currently, item can be shipped only within the U.S. and to APO/FPO addresses. For APO/FPO shipments, please check with the manufacturer regarding warranty and support issues.", "International Shipping": "This item is not eligible for international shipping.", "Date First Available": "October 29, 2016", "Price": "$2,249.99", "Product Name": "Apple MacBook Pro MLW72LL/A 15.4-inch Laptop with Touch Bar (2.6GHz quad-core Intel Core i7, 256GB Retina Display), Silver"},
{"Screen Size": "13.3 inches", "Screen Resolution": "2560-by-1600", "Max Screen Resolution": "2560-by-1600", "Processor": "2.9 GHz Intel Core i5", "RAM": "8 GB LPDDR3", "Memory Speed": "2133 MHz", "Hard Drive": "256 GB", "Graphics Coprocessor": "Intel Iris Graphics 550", "Card Description": "integrated", "Wireless Type": "802.11B, 802.11G, 802.11n", "Brand Name": "Apple", "Item model number": "MLH12LL/A", "Hardware Platform": "Mac", "Operating System": "Mac OS Sierra", "Item Weight": "3 pounds", "Product Dimensions": "8.4 x 12 x 0.6 inches", "Item Dimensions  L x W x H": "8.36 x 11.97 x 0.59 inches", "Color": "Space Gray", "Processor Brand": "Intel", "Processor Count": "1", "Computer Memory Type": "DDR3 SDRAM", "Flash Memory Size": "256", "Battery Type": "Lithium Polymer (LiPo)", "ASIN": "B01LTHXA5O", "Customer Reviews": "", "Best Sellers Rank": "", "Shipping Weight": "5.7 pounds (", "Domestic Shipping": "Currently, item can be shipped only within the U.S. and to APO/FPO addresses. For APO/FPO shipments, please check with the manufacturer regarding warranty and support issues.", "International Shipping": "This item is not eligible for international shipping.", "Date First Available": "October 29, 2016", "Price": "$1,649.99", "Product Name": "Apple MacBook Pro MLH12LL/A 13.3-inch Laptop with Touch Bar (2.9GHz dual-core Intel Core i5, 256GB Retina Display), Space Gray"},
{"Screen Size": "14 inches", "Screen Resolution": "1920x1080", "Max Screen Resolution": "1920x1080", "Processor": "1.6 GHz Intel Celeron", "RAM": "4 GB DDR3 SDRAM", "Hard Drive": "32 GB SSD", "Graphics Coprocessor": "Intel HD Graphics", "Chipset Brand": "Intel", "Card Description": "integrated", "Wireless Type": "802.11 A/C", "Brand Name": "Acer", "Series": "Acer Chromebook", "Item model number": "Acer Chromebook", "Hardware Platform": "PC", "Operating System": "Chrome OS", "Item Weight": "4.5 pounds", "Product Dimensions": "15.1 x 9.6 x 1 inches", "Item Dimensions  L x W x H": "15.1 x 9.6 x 0.97 inches", "Processor Brand": "Intel", "Processor Count": "4", "Computer Memory Type": "DDR3 SDRAM", "Power Source": "AC & Battery", "ASIN": "B01M9BPNSD", "Customer Reviews": "", "Best Sellers Rank": "", "Shipping Weight": "4.5 pounds (", "Date First Available": "October 16, 2016", "Price": "$274.00", "Product Name": "2016 Newest Acer 14 Inch FHD Premium Flagship Chromebook (IPS 1920x1080 Display, Intel Celeron Quad-Core N3160 Processor up to 2.24GHz, 4GB RAM, 32GB SSD, Wifi, Chrome OS) (Certified Refurbished)"},
{"Screen Size": "14 inches", "Max Screen Resolution": "1366 x 768", "Processor": "2.1 GHz Pentium", "RAM": "4 GB SDRAM DDR4", "Hard Drive": "500 GB HDD 5400 rpm", "Graphics Coprocessor": "integrated_graphics", "Chipset Brand": "intel", "Card Description": "integrated", "Wireless Type": "802.11bgn", "Number of USB 2.0 Ports": "1", "Average Battery Life (in hours)": "8.5 hours", "Brand Name": "Lenovo", "Series": "Lenovo", "Item model number": "Flex 4", "Hardware Platform": "PC", "Operating System": "Windows 10", "Item Weight": "3.9 pounds", "Product Dimensions": "13.3 x 9.2 x 0.8 inches", "Item Dimensions  L x W x H": "13.3 x 9.2 x 0.8 inches", "Color": "Black", "Processor Brand": "Intel", "Processor Count": "2", "Computer Memory Type": "DDR3 SDRAM", "Hard Drive Interface": "Serial ATA", "Hard Drive Rotational Speed": "5400 RPM", "Power Source": "AC & Battery", "ASIN": "B01M30SA1R", "Customer Reviews": "", "Best Sellers Rank": "", "Shipping Weight": "5.6 pounds (", "Date First Available": "October 16, 2016", "Price": "$399.00", "Product Name": "2016 Newest Lenovo 14 Inch 2-in-1 Touchscreen Laptop PC, Intel Pentium Dual-Core Processor, 8.5-hour Battery Life, 4GB DDR4 RAM, 500GB HDD, WIFI, Webcam, HDMI, Bluetooth, Windows 10"},
{"Screen Size": "15.6 inches", "Max Screen Resolution": "1366 x 768", "Processor": "2 GHz", "RAM": "4 GB", "Hard Drive": "500 GB HDD", "Graphics Coprocessor": "radeon r4", "Chipset Brand": "amd", "Brand Name": "HP", "Series": "15-BA009DX", "Item model number": "15-BA009DX", "Operating System": "Windows 10", "Item Weight": "4.7 pounds", "Product Dimensions": "15.1 x 10 x 0.9 inches", "Item Dimensions  L x W x H": "15.1 x 10 x 0.9 inches", "Processor Brand": "AMD", "Processor Count": "4", "ASIN": "B01N8U0046", "Customer Reviews": "", "Best Sellers Rank": "", "Shipping Weight": "6.1 pounds", "Date First Available": "November 10, 2016", "Product Name": "HP 15-BA009DX - 15.6\" HD - AMD A6-7310 - 4GB Memory - 500GB HDD - Black"},
{"Screen Size": "14 inches", "Screen Resolution": "1366 x 768 pixels", "Max Screen Resolution": "1366 x 768 pixels", "Processor": "2.58 GHz Intel Celeron", "RAM": "4 GB DDR3L SDRAM", "Memory Speed": "1600 MHz", "Hard Drive": "16 GB SSD", "Graphics Coprocessor": "integrated_graphics", "Chipset Brand": "Intel HD Graphics", "Card Description": "Integrated", "Wireless Type": "802.11bgn", "Number of USB 2.0 Ports": "2", "Number of USB 3.0 Ports": "1", "Brand Name": "HP", "Series": "Chromebook", "Item model number": "T4M32UT#ABA", "Hardware Platform": "PC", "Operating System": "Chrome", "Item Weight": "7.2 ounces", "Product Dimensions": "18.5 x 11.7 x 3 inches", "Item Dimensions  L x W x H": "18.5 x 11.7 x 3 inches", "Color": "Silver", "Processor Brand": "Intel", "Processor Count": "2", "Computer Memory Type": "DDR3 SDRAM", "Flash Memory Size": "16.0", "Optical Drive Type": "None", "Battery Type": "Lithium-Ion (Li-Ion)", "ASIN": "B016J9LHSO", "Customer Reviews": "", "Best Sellers Rank": "", "Shipping Weight": "5 pounds (", "Domestic Shipping": "Amazon only ships this item within the contiguous 48 United States. Other Sellers on Amazon may ship this item to Alaska, Hawaii and US Territories.", "International Shipping": "This item is not eligible for international shipping.", "Date First Available": "October 14, 2015", "Price": "$252.95", "Product Name": "HP 14\" Chromebook 14 G4, 4 GB RAM, 16 GB SSD, Intel HD Graphics, Black (T4M32UT#ABA)"}
]